<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Moby | Become a smarter investor in just 5 minutes</title>
    <description>We send you daily investing strategies, stock research, and crypto analysis that's fun to read and easy to digest. Join today for free and start making smarter investing decisions.</description>
    <link>https://www.moby.co/blog.rss</link>
    <item>
      <title>2 Stocks Making Waves In The Global Global Shipping Phenomenon</title>
      <description>&lt;div data-mobiledoc="'{&amp;quot;version&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;0.3.2&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;atoms&amp;quot;:[],&amp;quot;cards&amp;quot;:[[&amp;quot;image&amp;quot;,{&amp;quot;src&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;https://www.moby.co/content/images/2021/08/Copy-of-Copy-of-New-Report-Published--16--min.jpg&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;width&amp;quot;:960,&amp;quot;height&amp;quot;:960,&amp;quot;caption&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;The" new="" york="" trading="" port="" one="" of="" the="" most="" popular="" ports="" in="" world="" hr="" html="" :="" --="" tradingview="" widget="" begin=""&gt;
&lt;div class="\&amp;quot;tradingview-widget-container\&amp;quot;"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you haven't been paying attention lately, inflation is a massive problem in the global economy. It's difficult to pinpoint the root issue but it is a combination of commodity prices, supply chain issues, demand spikes, etc.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color: #06cbf8;"&gt;However, the one that flies most under the radar is &lt;u&gt;shipping costs&lt;/u&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In the US, these costs are extremely visible because most of the goods consumed are imported. Therefore the subsequent rise in shipping costs often get passed onto the end consumer. When looking further into the shipping costs, we see that in the last year alone, shipping from China to the US has risen over 500%. This means that in today's prices, it costs roughly $20,000 for one shipping container on a route from China to New York! As a massive importer of Chinese goods, this leaves the American consumer highly susceptible to this increase in shipping costs.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;While this is becoming a massive problem within itself, as investors, we're always trying to smell out an opportunity. And in this case, there's a few stocks with opportunity for massive upside potential!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;And guess what? There's someone very famous who is already in on it too.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;His name: Michael Burry.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;&lt;strong&gt;More on his take:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Does this name sound familiar? If not, he is the investor who has is famous for shorting the economy before the great recession in 07/08. His short is so famous they ended up making the movie, "The Big Short" after his move. And guess what? This is his next bet.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Our Investment Thesis:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So what is the opportunity?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color: #06cbf8;"&gt;We're making investments into the shipping companies themselves!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As the primary beneficiaries of the increase in cost, these companies are standing by, looking at massive revenue increases almost overnight at nearly the same margins. While a lot of these companies have already benefitted to date (see their stock prices below), we believe this trend will continue.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Why? Largely because we do not believe shipping costs will drop anytime soon. This is due to two main reasons:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The first is due to the way shipping contracts are structured. They're often locked in at annual rates and many suppliers have no choice but to accept them. Additionally, with the number of contracts signed, it looks like they also believe that shipping costs are only going to rise. By locking in contracts now, they hedge any future increase in cost until the contract is up!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The second reason is due to the brands themselves. During a recent interview with the CEO of Proctor &amp;amp; Gamble &lt;em&gt;(the company behind brands such as Downy, Gain, Tide, Febreze, and Dawn)&lt;/em&gt;, the CEO alluded to the recent increases in shipping costs. He very calmly stated that he fully anticipates on passing these costs down to the consumer and absorbing next to no losses. Until brands start changing their mentality around, or consumers stop buying their products, they're going to be in no position to deny or negotiate on costs with the shipping companies.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The key takeaway here is that we, nor Michael, believe shipping costs will be decreasing any time soon. Therefore, as we stated above, we believe these companies below will be prime beneficiaries and experience continued stock appreciation!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;&lt;strong&gt;So which stocks are they?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;h3 style="padding-left: 30px;"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;1) Genco Shipping &amp;amp; Trading Limited (GNK)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The first stock is Genco. Genco Shipping &amp;amp; Trading Limited is a leading provider of international seaborne dry-bulk transportation services. Their stock is up over 80% this year but we believe this has potential to keep running up! While the upside is high here, this pick does come with a lot of risk!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 style="padding-left: 30px;"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;2)&amp;nbsp;⬇️&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Oct 2021 17:59:56 +0300</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.moby.co/blog/2-stocks-making-waves-in-the-global-global-shipping-phenomenon</link>
      <guid>https://www.moby.co/blog/2-stocks-making-waves-in-the-global-global-shipping-phenomenon</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supply Chain Crisis: Shipping, Evergrande &amp; More</title>
      <description>&lt;p style="text-align: center;"&gt;&lt;iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/yuvxujk-VE8" title="YouTube video player" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen"&gt; &lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align: left;"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color: #06cbf8;"&gt;If you want to watch the full video where we break down current conditions, Evergrande, outlook, etc. check out the above. For the shorter, actionable version just keep reading out.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align: left;"&gt;&lt;span style="color: #332f4f;"&gt;COVID and bad boating has brought the topic of &amp;ldquo;global supply chains&amp;rdquo; to the forefront of the news over the past year. Today we&amp;rsquo;re going to take a look at just how complex global supply chains are and how this tangled web affects you as a consumer.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color: #332f4f;"&gt;Take a look at the smartphone. If you were asked, where are iPhones made? Your answer would probably be China. While it is assembled in China by Foxconn, all of the parts that go into an iPhone are manufactured across 43 different countries before they end up on store shelves. The lithium in the batteries are mined in Brazil, semiconductors are printed in Taiwan, and the iPhone boxes are manufactured in the Czech Republic to name a few.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color: #332f4f;"&gt;Now here&amp;rsquo;s an important realization -&amp;gt; If any critical part of this supply chain is disrupted or delayed, the entire product is disrupted or delayed! This is the push and pull of managing a global supply chain where a company has to juggle between lowering costs and resiliency so delays and disruptions don&amp;rsquo;t become showstoppers.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;&lt;span style="color: #332f4f;"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Why are global supply chains so complex?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color: #332f4f;"&gt;A company like Apple sells the iPhone, but they don&amp;rsquo;t manufacture a single component themselves. Every single piece is subcontracted out to specialists and the final product is assembled by Foxconn. This supply chain complexity is typical in most products that you see today in every single vertical from the hamburger you have at McDonalds all the way to the COVID vaccine from Moderna.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color: #332f4f;"&gt;So let&amp;rsquo;s talk about why this happens:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: #332f4f;"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Minimizing Costs&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: #332f4f;"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Taxes&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: #332f4f;"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Lobbying&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color: #332f4f;"&gt;Minimizing costs is the easiest to understand. Companies are built to maximize shareholder value so reducing the cost to produce their products is often one of the biggest focuses within a company. Raw materials aren&amp;rsquo;t available everywhere in the world so different components need to be sourced from where they can be mined or harvested from. For example, lithium is an essential component in all modern batteries. Australia is the largest producer of the world&amp;rsquo;s lithium at 52.9% while Chile has the largest reserve of lithium in the world at 55.5%. The lithium has to be mined and then transported to a facility that produces batteries, then shipped out to the country where the product is assembled and then out to where it&amp;rsquo;ll be finally sold. Depending on the costs within a country and the current cost of shipping, it may make sense to weave what seems like an enormously complex web and at the end of the day, have the cheapest product at the right quality.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color: #332f4f;"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Now to make this even more complex, let&amp;rsquo;s add in lobbying and taxes. &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color: #332f4f;"&gt;APN311 is one of the leading drugs to treat high-risk neuroblastoma. This, as well as many other essential drug components, is produced out of Austria, one of the most expensive places on earth to produce something. It&amp;rsquo;s made here because the government has invested in an incredibly robust Research and Development infrastructure for drug research within Austria with the tradeoff being any breakthrough drug developed in the state-sponsored facilities is required to be produced in Austria. This is seen as a win-win because the pharmaceutical companies are able to access a wealth of medical research and the residents of Austria get access to a large number of high-paying pharmaceutical manufacturing jobs.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color: #332f4f;"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Now that we&amp;rsquo;ve established that Austria produces one of the essential ingredients for APN311, why is it that China is the main manufacturer?&lt;/strong&gt; This comes down to taxes. Countries have certain trade deals that dramatically influence how this supply chain web looks. Import taxes can oftentimes be steep, which can heavily influence the final price of the product.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color: #332f4f;"&gt;On the other hand, countries that have special trade relations offer enormous tax savings if the supply chain is routed through them appropriately. Austria is part of the European Union, which means products can be traded freely between Austria and Ireland. Ireland is home to a specific duty-free zone that can export goods to China without any tariffs to be packaged and then all of a sudden, APN311 is a product of china with a component from Austria. As a Chinese product, it can now be exported into any country that has made trade deals with China which is quite a few countries.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color: #332f4f;"&gt;This is a fairly simplified supply chain to demonstrate what factors may influence the supply chain and add to the complexity. Most companies never disclose their entire supply chain so oftentimes a consumer won&amp;rsquo;t know why certain products are delayed or discontinued. One of the important things to pay attention to when looking at any company that produces a physical product, especially a complex product, is its reliance on single-source suppliers. When Tesla first began ramping up their production in the fiscal year of 2013, they were sourcing 2,000+ parts from 300 suppliers where most of them were single-source suppliers. This means that if any one of the single-source providers were delayed and Tesla ran out of that product in the production line, all production would have been halted until that part arrived at the production line.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;&lt;span style="color: #332f4f;"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Hedging Against Supply Chain Risks:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color: #332f4f;"&gt;But now flash forward to 2018 and Tesla now has many partners to source their components and has reduced its reliance on single-source suppliers to minimize risk. And as of late they've moved more and more to a vertical integrated model.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color: #06cbf8;"&gt;This is where it gets interesting!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color: #332f4f;"&gt;While it is very expensive to become vertically integrated, once integrated, you're able to start raising margins and hedge out most supply chain risks - because you're the entire chain. If one component of your output gets delayed or a factory goes out of business, you need not worry because everything is done in house! While this model is hard to recreate, looking out for companies that are able to do this or are on their way there is a sign of mastery that shouldn't be ignored. While it is hard to quantify this in traditional analysis, a mark of this is paramount to a strong forward looking business model. The biggest benefits in addition to this are, lower transportation costs and turnaround times, reduced disruptions and quality problems from suppliers and improved profitability.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;So with that context, here are three strong companies who are working in the right direction.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color: #332f4f;"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Shell (RDS.A):&lt;/strong&gt; Remember this recent post on &lt;span style="text-decoration: underline;"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.moby.co/products/premium-investing-research/categories/2148721435/posts/2152231592" style="color: #332f4f; text-decoration: underline;"&gt;Shell&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;?&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Shell has&amp;nbsp;exploration divisions that seek new sources of oil and subsidiaries that are devoted to extracting and refining it. Their transportation divisions transport the finished product. Their retail divisions operate the gas stations that deliver their product. From start to finish, Shell is a part of the exploration process all the way to end sales with the user themselves. The output is extraordinary and is the reason Shell is a top pick for us in the energy sector. True vertical integration is hard to achieve and Shell is a model citizen for how to do it!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color: #332f4f;"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Netflix (NFLX):&lt;/strong&gt; Netflix's path to vertical integration has been a long ride. Once they realized they could improve margins by producing some of their own original&amp;nbsp;content, they moved from a DVD distributor to a vertically integrated player.&amp;nbsp;Today, Netflix uses its distribution model to promote its original content alongside programming licensed from studios and should be a force for years to come. We have and continue to be long the company!&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: #332f4f;"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Peloton (PTON):&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;Don't think Peloton is vertically integrated? They're sneakily more-so then you would think. For example, rather than using someone else's bike, they designed and manufacturer their own bike from the ground up with its own hardware and software. Rather than outsource classes and instructors they do everything in-house. Rather than put these instructors in pre-built studios, they stood up their own and bought their own store front. In addition they stood up their own retail stores rather than going through a third party. At every turn&amp;nbsp;Peloton&amp;nbsp;optimized for vertical integration even though that meant a longer and more expensive go to market. While the stock has been hit hard YTD due to a return to gym culture, we think the business should bounce back in the long term. Its a high risk pick but the valuation is finally starting to come in check!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;&lt;span style="color: #332f4f;"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Bonus: Tesla (TSLA):&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: #332f4f;"&gt;We know we said three but Tesla is an obvious choice for this as well. So let's count this as a bonus. But with news of them moving large parts of their operations to Texas, Tesla is the model citizen for vertical integration! As we've been mentioning for the last few years, this is a buy and hold stock to keep over the next decade!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Oct 2021 17:57:23 +0300</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.moby.co/blog/evergrande</link>
      <guid>https://www.moby.co/blog/evergrande</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Moby Live: Bitcoin All Time High's, Facebook Scandals, Supply Chain Shortages &amp; More</title>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color: #bacfe7;"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Audio Recorded on October 21, 2021 (Transcript below)&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color: #06cbf8;"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;For Audio Version, Become a Moby Premium Member&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr /&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Peter Starr:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400;"&gt; Q4 is obviously pretty wild. It is half an hour before the market closes, and this is a Thursday just chock full of solid earnings, which is driving the S and P to new highs.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400;"&gt;I mean, what is it? Tesla rose 3% unimproved gross margins. I think they went up 30 and a half percent on its automotive business and somewhere around 25 for other business, which for the last five quarters is another record. Netflix spiked pretty well off with the success with squid game, which is hilarious, watching a very anticapitalist TV show, single handedly prop up our HELOC capitalist market, the chips shortages, and slowing Invidia down for whatever reason.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400;"&gt;3% and we work,&amp;nbsp; , his back from the dead going up 13% after their cute little speck launch. I mean, it's not all rosy though. Apple claimed its first victim today with their new privacy policy. Snap is down 25% for the missed revenue goals. Hard, thanks to apple turning up tracking. So all in all, a really wild day, copping off kind of a really wild week.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400;"&gt;I guess, Justin, the main question we have here in the audience is are we going to start seeing the market get even more volatile now that we're starting to exit the more exciting part of earnings season? Or do you think the market can keep this rally going through? It'll be a tough Q4. Like it really feels like all the services we're seeing are making this just completely avoid inflationary pressure right now.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Justin Kramer:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400;"&gt; I mean, I think you're better suited to answer the question. Super comprehensive,This is&amp;nbsp; something we've been paying attention to. So when the market hit, you know, two, three weeks ago it was crashing and everyone's worried and we just said, don't worry, it's going to rebound.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400;"&gt;And then you have weeks like this, where it's hitting all time highs again, this is just part of like the upward cycle higher. So the valuation ratio ratios, the earnings of the S and P 500, the PE ratio of the S P 500. These are things that, although things are expensive it's because things are growing so quickly.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400;"&gt;And we saw such a peel back,&amp;nbsp; , in a lot of sectors due to COVID that a lot of this is like supercharged demand that is finally coming to pick back up. So a lot of these sectors and companies are a little depressed in their earnings, even though their valuations are high because they're just lagging their potential.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400;"&gt;So it may stunt growth here in the. Like overall in the long-term again, until things fundamentally change, inflation's picking back up. People are still willing to pay the prices for now. We're continuing to be long. If inflation spikes another 5%, then, then maybe this conversation changes. But given where we are today and where it looks like things are headed.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400;"&gt;We're still going to be long. And then you, you mentioned the Snapchat things, some privacy related concerns kind of put out a slam piece on Facebook about a week or two ago, talks about iOS 14 and a half and how it's going to be potentially the downfall, a lot of their advertising platform. And so when Snapchat comes out today, they report earnings and they're down 25% after hours.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400;"&gt;This is not going to be a challenge that is isolated just to them. This is going to be a wide-field issue around Facebook, around other social media giants. Pinterest. We have a piece of later coming out on Pinterest and PayPal and the rumors there. And so this is going to be a problem for a lot of platforms out there, especially on mobile,&amp;nbsp; as tracking and, and third party cookies comes to an end.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400;"&gt;So. Long story short stimulation on the market, a lot of headwinds for data privacy and some advertising platforms, but overall things are trending holistically and in the right direction.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Peter Starr:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400;"&gt; Exactly like overall, like outside of the media and advertising industrial complex, you're seeing a lot of positive signs too, as you know, money tends to flow in a lot of different directions.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400;"&gt;So I want to add on top of those SNAP conversations. Audience, I want you to put two facts together real fast here. Snapchat went down 25% today and they've basically blamed them missing revenue on Apple's new privacy settings. So also keep in mind that yesterday. Weirdly announces that they want to completely rebrand and then also be entirely a metaverse company.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400;"&gt;And you're seeing Facebook try to reshift its entire ecosystem so they can have way more control over their audience and not even need to rely on, you know, a multi-platform approach with the Facebook pixel has. So watch these market pressures play out in real time. It's amazing how much Apple has changed the game in terms of advertising.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400;"&gt;Kat and galvanized a lot of really insane growth. Like I'm so excited for the metaverse. I'm so excited for all these developments, but that's mostly me as a creator because I S I succeed if I have new and interesting places to talk. Right. So keep that in mind. Like, we're seeing a lot of energy, like, this is one of those situations,&amp;nbsp; and not to be all weird or anything, but this is one of those situations where there's kind of like a month-long period where decades happen as opposed to, you know, several months where nothing happens.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400;"&gt;So,&amp;nbsp; I'm really excited just to watch all that shake out. But I think. Like looking in the comments, looking in the questions. A lot of us are very concerned about the volatility we see here in the stock market. And so a lot of us are thinking about other places to put our money. And so this gives me a nice little segue, Justin, into some research.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400;"&gt;I believe yesterday, it was yesterday's research where you were talking about Apollo and talking about investing in the private market. And I said just when it gets through your thoughts, in terms of what it means to invest like in the primary market, as opposed to the secondary market and what the value there is, like, what are your thoughts in terms of thinking about finding those new avenues to invest?&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400;"&gt;Like a lot of people are running to fundraise for retail. What's your, what are your, what are your hot, what are your top level takes on Apollo and how to invest in the, in the primary market, as opposed to the secondary?&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Justin Kramer:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400;"&gt; Yeah. So just real quick to kind of piggyback on the challenge of that before,&amp;nbsp; , about Snapchat and Facebook and the metaverse, you know, Snapchat's down 25% today, and Facebook hasn't even reported down 5% after hours.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400;"&gt;So investors are gonna start seeing the trend.&amp;nbsp; and so to your point, creating like this, this new context or who their company is going to be a year ago, it was, they tried to launch their own crypto. It kind of really went nowhere. Now it's this metaphor. They're seeing kind of the way to the end of the tunnel.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400;"&gt;And they realize that social media, especially from Facebook's perspective, is not necessarily going to be their long game. Instagram is still crushing WhatsApp, a lot of the other platforms, but they're, they're definitely looking to pivot in some capacity as they,&amp;nbsp; , they see a lot of things changing.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400;"&gt;So it's a really interesting thing to watch.&amp;nbsp; and again, that's why we called it out last week, made a video on. You know, something we're watching really closely.&amp;nbsp; but yeah, outside of that kind of relating more towards your, your later question as it is for Apollo. And this is like something that we've been wanting to write about for a long time.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400;"&gt;Um, Especially with the rise of crypto and people investing in other assets. It's like, okay, well our equities, what they used to be, are there better returns elsewhere? Can we invest in crypto? How do I invest in private companies? Can I invest in real estate? Can I invest in all these things that historically I haven't had access to?&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400;"&gt;And today the answer is largely no. Or the ease of doing it as hard as we know.&amp;nbsp; but as more and more options kind of opened up. Those in theory should become easier, but there still are ways via the equity market to get access to those types of investments. And there's a company called Apollo that most people, if you've never heard of, they're, they're a large asset manager.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400;"&gt;And by. Investing in them, maybe it's not one-to-one exposure, but you're getting access to their entire portfolio. And so that their direct kind of results in terms of like their operating profits and what makes a stock go up and down is strictly incumbent upon the investments they make and all their investments are in real estate.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400;"&gt;In startup tech companies and crypto and all these areas. So you're kind of getting a culmination more or less of everything they do wrapped into an ETF or sorry into an equity rather. And you can invest in them, get in, get out super fast. It's a way to get exposure, like broad, broad exposure to all these traditional or less traditional rather asset classes.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400;"&gt;You know, 99% of the population doesn't have, you know, most people can't go out there and buy an apartment building and get passive income via the rental. It's just, it's just not feasible. So like, this is a really good way for people,&amp;nbsp; for I'm sure a lot of people here get exposure, do it cheaply, do it quickly.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400;"&gt;And if things don't work out, you can get out fast. Whereas know if you're obviously going to try and sell a billion. It's going to take some time, take some money. It's not so challenging. This is a really good alternative. Something that we've had our eyes on for a while. And they're kind of in the middle of a rapid growth phase right now.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400;"&gt;So it's a cool way to get exposure and not have to spend too much time digging into what's the best building. What's the best startup company? What's the best crypto we're calling? It's just, you know, they're doing kind of the hard work for you. And that's a, that's where you're participating with, with their stock.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Peter Starr:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400;"&gt; Precisely. And that's a lot of the reason why we are always so bullish on ETFs too. Like it's, it's great getting access to all this private stuff, but getting access to something more institutionally managed as well. So that's why I'm bullish on this as on Apollo as well, and just like excited to have that kind of exposure, because right now the name of the game genuinely is diversification because with the amount of energy that we're experiencing in this economy right now, it's really hard to see where things are going to go.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400;"&gt;I looked, I looked this week and I saw the earnings calls coming up and I thought about what various short-term plays I was going to make. And I was like, I literally sold some Chipotle lay stock because I didn't want to have any real huge exposure to what I thought was going to be rising.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400;"&gt;Prices. But instead of that, they crushed estimates. Their sales jumped 22% and their stock is now, well, it's flat now, but it went up pretty hard today. So it's really hard to predict precisely where all this energy is going to go. Who's going to win and who's going to lose because of. Heat in this economy.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400;"&gt;You think you think the market's going to Zig and it's going to zag. It's just the amount of upturns and downturns you're going to see. I never thought Nvidia would go with, have it, have it, stock price, go up. But it's just, you know, doing so well, despite a ridiculous chip shortage with a lot of, there's a lot of good gaming news coming out and, you know, sales are up.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400;"&gt;I mean their earnings aren't till November, but there's still a lot of good sentiment driving their stock price up today. So that's the main thing to keep in mind. This is just so fundamentally hard to predict. And the ups and downs are just going to be a lot sharper during a period like this, which is pretty nutty considering we're here in Q4.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400;"&gt;So,&amp;nbsp; God help you if you're a day trader and also just like good, like if you, you know, make all the right moves, it's a great time to be a day trader, but it's not really a philosophy that we super,&amp;nbsp; endorse, but that kind of gets me into various other ways. The market is diversifying.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400;"&gt;&amp;nbsp;And last week we talked about the coming rise in crypto and low and behold, not to like pat ourselves on the back or anything, but like almost right on schedule Bitcoin hit new all time highs. Thanks to leveraging Bitcoins now down to about 62. So literally we talked about Bitcoin at 60. Now we're talking about it at 62, as opposed to it at 6 K&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400;"&gt;So, what's your view overall of the crypto space right now? I mean, I understand like it's impossible to predict, but looking at this, do you see this, this October is more of a bull trap or the start of a bull run? Like, what is your feeling right now in the crypto space, as Bitcoin goes through this kind of goofy little hiccup?&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Justin Kramer:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400;"&gt; Yeah. I mean, a lot of crypto kind of just in general follows trends. I mean, we're not really ones for our technical analysis, but. If you look at the crypto space. So like there, there's definitely a common theme in terms of you can use kind of past,&amp;nbsp; kind of pass indicators to, to start predicting forward prices, whereas in the equity markets.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400;"&gt;So we'll be more challenging to do. And so if you look back over the last, like five years in even, or even earlier this year, you saw the spike.&amp;nbsp; , kind of late 2020, it was around 20,000 and it surges up to 60 and four months. It goes back down to the thirties for a while. And then obviously over the last month or two, it's really gone crazy.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400;"&gt;And you go back to 2017, it's floating in the, the two to 5,000 range. It spikes up to 20 or close to it. And then it goes back down into, like, again, the mid kind of 5,000 range&amp;nbsp; , for a few years until it spikes back up again. So, you know, Bitcoin doesn't have a tremendous history. I mean, it's only obviously been around for so long, so it's hard to say, oh, this happened before it'll happen again.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400;"&gt;But using the indicators that we use, a lot of the proprietary tools. Yeah, it does look like it's starting to approach a point where there could be some sort of inflection point where either there'll be a crash and it'll likely start like recovering to a certain level, stay there for a while until it makes its move upwards or kind of then spike upwards, and maybe hit 70 to 80 K before making that eventual move downwards.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400;"&gt;We're looking at the charts in real time. And we're kind of at an interesting point where it could go either way. I'm not probably the answer everyone wants to hear, but it's kind of the truth right now. So for us, as short-term from a short-term mindset, we weren't allocating too much more. We already have some pretty heavy exposure.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400;"&gt;And then over the long-term, as you know, Called out before we're continuing to just dollar cost average in. If we see opportunities to buy in cheap, we'll get in.&amp;nbsp; This is something we fundamentally believe in over the longterm. Last year, we wrote a piece about how we thought it was going to go to a 100K. I mean, there's a real chance that it will happen this year, if not next.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400;"&gt;And so it's really the long-term game here. NFTs are slowly starting to cool off. So you need to pick your opportunities wisely. And again -- it's the responsible yet boring answer. Everyone wants to get rich overnight. We realize it's not, it's not fun waiting, but this is an asset class that is still very, very young and still has a ton of room to run.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400;"&gt;So, you know, the TLDR of all this. If you want to get in over the long-term great, you know, it's hard to pick the top. It's hard to pick the bottom.&amp;nbsp; but if you're, if you're short-term trading it, we would, we'd likely stay away for now. There's a lot of, a lot of downward pressure potentially coming.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Peter Starr:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400;"&gt; Because what you're watching is that incredible spike from 60 to 67, over a 48 hour period, kind of drove a lot of leveraged interest into the space. And that's where you're going to get a lot of the really heavy volatility people borrowing heavily.&amp;nbsp; , to get into these leveraged positions that can just completely wipe themselves out.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400;"&gt;Bitcoin is not a place where you place your huge, huge bets. You incrementally increase your bet over time, ride this wave as best as you can. I think it's still going to go up from here by in a little bit, with that light light,&amp;nbsp; , that money you're going to want to light on fire and then get out when you think you're nearing that peak, because that peak always leads to a pretty significant crash.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400;"&gt;A lot of people start baling. One thing I saw in 2017 was this absolutely incredible percentage switch where a lot of whales and older Bitcoin investors bought in really early in the rise and a lot of new investors bought and right before the top and kind of got washed until basically recently.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400;"&gt;So now's the time to kind of hang out and just wait it out and give yourself time to. Get the capital necessary to win the next bull run. Right? So if you're still new to Bitcoin, if you're still in a really small position, you're just kind of extending your speculative budget rate.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400;"&gt;Now, as you watch this go up. So the main thing is short, short Bitcoins really. Medium. Bitcoin's pretty interesting and long, long Bitcoin. I mean, I don't see any reason why I can't hit a hundred K.&amp;nbsp; but the, the question mark is now is a hundred K this year, or more like Q1 Q2 2022, but that gets us as we think more about the volatility as we think more about just again, all the energy in our economy.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400;"&gt;I think there's still a lot of interest, so I guess,&amp;nbsp; , we have time now to get right into audience questions as we sort of lay, the groundwork here. And I guess Justin, let's go back to snap real fast. You look, you look at snaps products, wheat, you look at the way they're playing this game.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400;"&gt;The main thing we have right now is is there any way, like, if you are, if you're Snapchat and you're thinking about like how to monetize.&amp;nbsp; , social media asset in this new paradigm shift with apple, is this a value play? Like, do you think this is something they figure out eventually? Or do you think this is just a sign of things to come for snap?&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400;"&gt;Like how do you, when you look at this, this is a hot take. Obviously I know, I can't ask you to give you real analysis on the spot here, but just looking at those facts right there. Is this a value playing by now and just assume it's a dip or do you think this is kind of like a harbinger of snap?&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Justin Kramer:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400;"&gt; Yeah. Again, similar to Facebook, I'm really a bit skeptical,&amp;nbsp; on kind of their overall business model. We dove into Facebook last week and it's really the same issue for,&amp;nbsp; , for Snapchat in the sense that, excuse me, sorry.&amp;nbsp; in the sense that they're dealing with a lot of data privacy.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400;"&gt;&amp;nbsp;You also in Facebook, for example, if anyone here has any advertising experience or spends any time there, Facebook is their bread and butter, is their lookalike audience, their ability to use day-to-day see on their platform to make. To make recommendations, then also use all the attribution that is done by third-party cookies to ultimately model out who the best people are.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400;"&gt;And that's why they've been really good at commanding a lot of ad spend because their ad network has been insane. And so with Apple rolling out iOS 14 and a half blocking a lot of the tracking that you can do across the internet.&amp;nbsp; Facebook has really, I mean, for the, one of the biggest tech companies in the world and.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400;"&gt;The one that has the most resources outside of maybe Tesla and one or two others, they are really challenged to find issues. So going over to Snapchat, they should be dealing with this just as hard, if not harder than Facebook is their ability to ultimately drive the same meaningful ad experience.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400;"&gt;Keep your customer acquisition costs down while increasing the lifetime value of your customers and finding the right one. They're just going to continue having a harder and harder time if you factor in other social platforms that are becoming bigger. This, you know, inherent metaverse that Facebook and others have alluded to.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400;"&gt;And for me, getting behind Snapchat over a multi-year time period is tough for me to say, I, personally wouldn't do it.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Peter Starr:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400;"&gt; And to really drive that home too, just to give you some more examples. If you've been in New York, In the past year and a half, like literally anywhere. Like if you're the kind of person who walks across the bridges or you're the kind of person who goes to Coney island, you've seen the, and then create an incredible proliferation of these obnoxious barges that just have visual billboards on them.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400;"&gt;There just seemed to be more and more and more of them. And for me, that's a real visceral sign of just how,&amp;nbsp; on how advertising itself. The entire advertising industrial complex is really beginning to lose a lot of age and a lot of efficacy. And so I'm very concerned about advertising in general right now, because so much of the ads industry probably was carried by conversion data.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400;"&gt;Like you were able to really laser in your ad spend based on being able to track somebody from Facebook, all the way to your website, all the way through their entire customer lifetime, really. And that's definitely going away. And without that kind of cost efficiency, there's an inflection point that may have already passed.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400;"&gt;However, that doesn't change certain other completely different approaches to advertising, which is what makes tick talks so incredible because tick tock doesn't need to rely on. Conversion metrics. They are an incredible platform for virality, for old-school advertising, which is just exposure campaigns, like really big advertisers, throwing a lot of money to get as many eyeballs on their brand as possible.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400;"&gt;That's something that's still effective. It's one of those really wild things where we've completely gone back to like 1995 in terms of our ads paradigm. As these data privacy laws get more and more robust. And companies like Apple just completely piece out like half the. Is off the, the, the tracking cycle now.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400;"&gt;So you're losing a lot of efficacy in advertising, but at the same time, certain different approaches to advertising will therefore become more effective. So,&amp;nbsp; I wish I could invest in TikTok right now, because I feel like it still has a strong position as a virality and exposure engine, as opposed to a conversion tracking.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400;"&gt;So I agree with you, Justin. Like it's one of those things where we're really in the woods right now, in terms of, should we be investing in anything that's a part of this industrial ads complex, Facebook and Google are going to be fine. I mean, they own the entire advertising internet, but they have lots of other things that they can fall back on as this becomes very like a very interesting place to be.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400;"&gt;I'm really interested about YouTube ads as well. And seeing if that sort of loses its efficacy, as all of this plays out. I'll have to see, we'll have to see, you know, Google learnings too, I guess,&amp;nbsp; we're, we're really approaching the end here, Justin. We want to make sure we keep this to a tight, tight 30 since we didn't have any technical issues this time.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400;"&gt;So that brings me to one quick, I'm going to give you a quick situation. I'm going to give you another quick,&amp;nbsp; , by the dip scenario brought to us by our audience. And I understand once again, you might've had a chance to do a lot of research. But I want to get your thoughts. People are, people watch the Nvidia news and they're like, okay, some companies just don't care about the chip shortage right now, Intel is down pretty hard.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400;"&gt;Um, their shares fell about 6% today on, you know, a weaker than expected sales report.&amp;nbsp; their EPS was 1.71 versus one point 11 expected, and the revenue was only 18 billion adjusted versus an 18.2, 4 billion expected. So they're. You know, basically off of the, the chip shortage off of like reduced sales.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400;"&gt;So if you look at companies like Intel and you watch this microchip shortage,&amp;nbsp; do you see companies like Intel is a value player by the dip? And like, as the chip shortage wanes that stock prices will go back up or are we entering another paradigm shift as the chip shortage just kind of gets exacerbated and people are talking about it lasting into 2023 again, totally get it.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400;"&gt;But what are your high level thoughts re: intel?&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Justin Kramer:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400;"&gt; Yeah, that's a good question.&amp;nbsp; and this is something we have been looking at.&amp;nbsp; Just, I mean, chip shortage in general is obviously hurting a lot of companies. The supply chain issue is just it's, it's not going away and it's been a problem for awhile.&amp;nbsp; So yeah, this is definitely something like we're looking at.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400;"&gt;For us, I mean, new Vidia kind of versus Intel,&amp;nbsp; , to, in our opinion, it's, it's, it's like comparing apples and oranges.&amp;nbsp; while Intel had,&amp;nbsp; you know, they had ships in like apple computers when apple started releasing their own processors, like with the M one and M two that. Kind of put a damper on a lot of things like Intel's growth.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400;"&gt;Um, if it's a funny sign that, but on Intel's steady, steady, slow growth, where in a video, for example, they're not reliant on one company like that. They're expanding faster than pretty much any other chip manufacturer out there. And so when you see the stock for them being up like 73% today,&amp;nbsp; , and then even after hours, they're pretty flat relative to Intel to your point of being down 10% after hours.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400;"&gt;And they're only up 12% today. Again, it kind of goes back to apples and oranges. So. To answer the kind of audience question here. No, I don't think Intel, this is a good buying opportunity for them. I mean, they're only up 60% in the last five years. Yes. They pay a dividend of two and a half percent, but if you're looking for yield, I think there's better opportunities out there.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400;"&gt;And if you're looking for growth opportunities with not a ton of risk, I also think there's better opportunities out there. So we've kind of been a little bit. Hands-off Intel for a while now. And, and we, we do feel that way with,&amp;nbsp; , a few of the other tech giants as well. And in terms of like the more legacy brands.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400;"&gt;So like, &amp;nbsp; I know like Oracle, for example, is doing really well,&amp;nbsp; over the last year, but again, over the last five years, they're only up 150%, even though they're paying a relatively small dividend yet.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Peter Starr:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400;"&gt; So I haven't really felt the need to like, get more chip or tech stocks. They're like Nvidia has been like my entire play.&amp;nbsp; but that, you know, that's bringing us really close to that half hour. I think we've talked a lot about the energy in the economy. Kind of given a good sort of benchmark for where we are in terms of this inflationary cycle.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400;"&gt;We're seeing how services can kind of dodge inflationary pressure for a bit and keep driving the economy up. And even places in meatspace are doing pretty successfully as well. As you know, when you think about inflation and inflationary pressure, the only bands that have inflation are too much money chasing too few goods.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400;"&gt;And it looks like. Even though we're experiencing a lot of labor shortages. There's a little bit of production in other parts of the economy that are keeping up with those inflationary pressures. So it's kind of working out in a positive direction, as long as we get to a situation where, you know, production can keep up as long as we can get through these supply chain issues.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400;"&gt;The main thing, of course, being those supply chain issues have been brewing since about the beginning of 2020. And so if they're only coming to a head. Is it going to be the same amount of time to get out of there? And we're going to have to see that moving forward, but Justin again, thank you so much for your time today, man.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400;"&gt;This has been a really awesome conversation. I really love where we went with it, but any final thoughts from you as we begin to think about this really like a high moment and when it's potentially kind of roller coaster.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Justin Kramer:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400;"&gt; No. I mean, we, we just need to continue watching kind of just overall earnings watching inflation, if that picks up substantial, even though it obviously has over the last 12 months looking at certain assets, if they're becoming overbought to the point where it just doesn't make sense anymore, there could be an interesting inflection point in either direction,&amp;nbsp; , over the next quarter.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400;"&gt;Um, but again, right now, given the information we have, we're, we're continuing to be long. A lot of our positions, we've had a value tilt moose this year, which has done pretty nicely for us. The fact that we've kind of mitigated some of the super growth names.&amp;nbsp; and again, as a strategy, we're going to continue until, until things change otherwise.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400;"&gt;Um, as things potentially inflation picks it more that should, if only continue to kind of push,&amp;nbsp; , alpha towards the names that we're holding. So long story short. We're continuing to hold along.&amp;nbsp; Q4 is always an interesting time in the markets. You got a ton of money pouring in, especially in the consumer names, in terms of sales people, trying to hit their targets at the end of the year.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400;"&gt;Um, it's, it should always be an interesting time in the market. And again, we're working.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Peter Starr:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400;"&gt; Exactly. I'm so glad we chose to stop. Start this podcast in October. It was not an August or anything because Q3 was so boring by comparison. I'm really loving riding the wave here in Q4, but either way, Justin Kramer , co-founder and lead analyst here&amp;nbsp; at moby.co it's been really awesome having you on this call live.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400;"&gt;Thank you so much for all of your awesome questions. Again, if you have anything else, you can always just feel free to hit us up throughout the whole Moby verse here on discord. We love, you know, answering your questions and engaging with you and you know, doing the research you want us to do. This is a two way street, and we want to make sure that we are providing you the intelligence and research.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400;"&gt;You need to build a portfolio you want to have, as you become, as you continue to grow your wealth over time, either way, audiences really appreciate your time. I'm going to go ahead and read the credits here. Podcast is produced, produced, hosted, and voiced by me, Peter Starr, Northrop. You can find more about us over@mobi.co.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400;"&gt;Feel free to follow us here on discord. Follow us on YouTube as well. We just released an awesome video, kind of going deeper into our position on sofa. After a piece of research we released last week, follow us on Tik TOK, just so I can keep juicing that algorithm. I'm very close to figuring it out and getting people excited about the market.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400;"&gt;They're on the, on the clock app, either way, audience. I really appreciate your time. If you have any other questions, you can feel free to DM me directly as well. And for now, all I can say is I like to leave you with. Love and incremental gains. Everyone be well, thank you so much. Have a great day.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Oct 2021 19:25:50 +0300</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.moby.co/blog/moby-podcast-october</link>
      <guid>https://www.moby.co/blog/moby-podcast-october</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PayPal: Does An Acquisition of Pinterest Make Sense?</title>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color: #332f4f;"&gt;You may have seen the rumors that PayPal was looking to acquire Pinterest. If you haven't, then we're happy to break the news!&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color: #332f4f;"&gt;But in any case, many investors are left wondering, PayPal and Pinterest, why? How do those two companies make sense together? &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color: #332f4f;"&gt;Add in the fact that the price tag for Pinterest's would likely be over $39 billion, and many people are left puzzled.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color: #332f4f;"&gt;That's where we come in. We did all the hard and boring work for you.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color: #332f4f;"&gt;With PayPal recently hitting our price target we thought it was perfect timing&amp;nbsp;to get into the details on the acquisition, whether or not it makes sense and then&amp;nbsp;ultimately&amp;nbsp;answer the most important question: &lt;strong&gt;How will this affect PayPal's stock price?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;!-- TradingView Widget BEGIN --&gt;
&lt;div class="tradingview-widget-container"&gt;
&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;
&lt;script type="text/javascript" src="https://s3.tradingview.com/tv.js"&gt;// &lt;![CDATA[

// ]]&gt;&lt;/script&gt;
&lt;script type="text/javascript"&gt;// &lt;![CDATA[
new TradingView.MediumWidget(
  {
  "symbols": [
    [
      "State Street",
      "NASDAQ:PYPL|12M"
    ]
  ],
  "chartOnly": false,
  "width": "100%",
  "height": 400,
  "locale": "en",
  "colorTheme": "light",
  "gridLineColor": "rgba(6, 203, 248, 0)",
  "trendLineColor": "#06cbf8",
  "fontColor": "#332f4f",
  "underLineColor": "rgba(6, 203, 248, 0.3)",
  "underLineBottomColor": "rgba(6, 203, 248, 0)",
  "isTransparent": false,
  "autosize": false,
  "showFloatingTooltip": true,
  "scalePosition": "no",
  "scaleMode": "Normal",
  "fontFamily": "Trebuchet MS, sans-serif",
  "noTimeScale": false,
  "container_id": "tradingview_4b3c2"
}
  );
// ]]&gt;&lt;/script&gt;
&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Oct 2021 00:26:09 +0300</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.moby.co/blog/paypal-pinterest</link>
      <guid>https://www.moby.co/blog/paypal-pinterest</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to easily invest in Startups, Private Companies, &amp; Real Estate</title>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color: #332f4f;"&gt;If you've ever wanted to invest directly in startup's, private companies, real estate, or credit, you may have found it extremely difficult or impossible to do. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color: #332f4f;"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The inherent problem with this, is that these investments often yield returns that are hard to find elsewhere.&lt;/strong&gt; For example, while the risk is high, investing in tech startup's could have 1,000x returns. And by investing in real estate, you can find steady cash flow that is hard to replicate elsewhere (&lt;em&gt;with added tax benefits&lt;/em&gt;).&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color: #332f4f;"&gt;The reason this is so challenging for many is that investing in these types of assets come with unique challenges. The biggest three are often:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: #332f4f;"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Capital:&amp;nbsp;These types of investments often come with extremely high minimum's. &lt;/strong&gt;For example, if you wanted to invest directly in real estate, buying home's/business locations is obviously extremely expensive. This makes these types of investments near impossible for 99% of the population.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: #332f4f;"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Accreditation:&amp;nbsp;Investing directly into young startups or private companies often require investors to be accredited.&lt;/strong&gt; For example, in the US, accredited investors need to either have a net worth of $1,000,000 or have income match at least $200,000 annually for the last two years. Therefore, similar to the above, this excludes 99% of investors.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: #332f4f;"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Liquidity:&amp;nbsp;Even if you have the capital and are accredited, a huge problem with these types of investments are that they are illiquid.&lt;/strong&gt; That means that once invested, there are usually lock-up periods/difficulties where you can't withdraw your capital. For example, if you wanted to get out of your real estate investment, you'd likely need to list your property, find a buyer to buy your home, and then spend time and money closing with them. Conversely, the most liquid markets are often the equity markets where you can buy and sell your investments in minutes.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color: #332f4f;"&gt;Details aside, the summary is that these challenges make investing in these types of assets&amp;nbsp;difficult. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color: #332f4f;"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Wish there was a better option?&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;&lt;span style="color: #06cbf8;"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Enter: Apollo Global Management&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color: #332f4f;"&gt;Apollo is&amp;nbsp;a global alternative investment management firm that invests in credit, private equity, and real assets. They are&amp;nbsp;one of the world's largest asset managers!&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color: #332f4f;"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;But the reason this investment is so unique, is because by investing in them, you're able to get access to startup's, private companies, real estate, etc. in a cheap and easy way.&lt;/strong&gt; But not only do they give you access, but they are doing it better than anyone else right now. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color: #332f4f;"&gt;Let's get into it ⬇️&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;!-- TradingView Widget BEGIN --&gt;
&lt;div class="tradingview-widget-container"&gt;
&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;
&lt;script type="text/javascript" src="https://s3.tradingview.com/tv.js"&gt;// &lt;![CDATA[

// ]]&gt;&lt;/script&gt;
&lt;script type="text/javascript"&gt;// &lt;![CDATA[
new TradingView.MediumWidget(
  {
  "symbols": [
    [
      "State Street",
      "NYSE:APO|12M"
    ]
  ],
  "chartOnly": false,
  "width": "100%",
  "height": 400,
  "locale": "en",
  "colorTheme": "light",
  "gridLineColor": "rgba(6, 203, 248, 0)",
  "trendLineColor": "#06cbf8",
  "fontColor": "#332f4f",
  "underLineColor": "rgba(6, 203, 248, 0.3)",
  "underLineBottomColor": "rgba(6, 203, 248, 0)",
  "isTransparent": false,
  "autosize": false,
  "showFloatingTooltip": true,
  "scalePosition": "no",
  "scaleMode": "Normal",
  "fontFamily": "Trebuchet MS, sans-serif",
  "noTimeScale": false,
  "container_id": "tradingview_4b3c2"
}
  );
// ]]&gt;&lt;/script&gt;
&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;&lt;span style="color: #332f4f;"&gt;Apollo Overview:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color: #332f4f;"&gt;Apollo is one of our top stocks within the finance sector as we think the market is severely discounting their projected growth over the next few years. There are a few things in particular that we're looking at that should fuel their growth going forward. They are:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: #332f4f;"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Q1 Merger With Athene:&lt;/strong&gt; While a merger&amp;nbsp;alone isn't extremely exciting, the reason this is huge for the company is because this merger should make them eligible to be included in the S&amp;amp;P 500. By getting lumped into the S&amp;amp;P 500 index, ETF's and Mutual Funds across the world will buy up their stock, helping artificially boost prices without any fundamental changes to their business. When you factor in the buying power of these vehicles, the should create sizable return opportunities for investors.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: #332f4f;"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;AUM Growth to over $1T by 2027:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;This growth would lead them to double their current AUM in only 6 years. The reason we believe this can happen is due to management projections which have been very on target historically as well as the performance of their funds. In particular their credit line (&lt;em&gt;think real estate, lending, etc.&lt;/em&gt;) has outperformed over the lifetime of the fund. This combined with their equity business unit, should deliver the AUM needed to hit their goals. As AUM is their primary source of revenue, doubling AUM should give them a significant lever to grow faster than the market has them slotted for.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: #332f4f;"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;One of the largest addressable markets amongst their peers:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;Apollo invests in a large spectrum of private companies, real estate and credit that most of their competition does not. What we mean by that is that their mandate&amp;nbsp;stretches across many different types of investments within each one of these asset classes. For example, within real estate, Apollo invests in structured credit, consumer credit,&amp;nbsp;senior secured lending, leasing, commercial real estate lending (such as 1st mortgages, mezzanine, net lease, CMBS, credit tenant leases). The list goes on and on further but the key takeaway is that Apollo goes very deep vertically within each one of their asset classes. This depth gives them the opportunity to deploy capital more-so than their peers, giving them in advantage in not only returning alpha, but also generating outsized fee's&lt;/span&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;&lt;span style="color: #332f4f;"&gt;Summary:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color: #332f4f;"&gt;Apollo is growing their business almost faster than anyone in their space. When combining their growth, with macro tailwinds, we think the market is under-discounting the upside of this company. Pair that with the fact that you get liquidity and easier access to this type of asset class and the opportunity is not only smart but is&amp;nbsp;differentiated and diversified.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color: #332f4f;"&gt;This companies gives you a&amp;nbsp;unique way&amp;nbsp;to invest in assets that are typically only reserved by the 1%. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color: #06cbf8;"&gt;Therefore, they are one of our top financial plays and we love to their risk/reward profile!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color: #332f4f;"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr /&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color: #332f4f;"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color: #fa4441;"&gt;Price Target:&amp;nbsp;GO PREMIUM TO UNLOCK&amp;nbsp;🔓&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color: #fa4441;"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Rating:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color: #fa4441;"&gt;GO PREMIUM TO UNLOCK&amp;nbsp;🔓&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color: #fa4441;"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Target Date:&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;GO PREMIUM TO UNLOCK&amp;nbsp;🔓&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color: #332f4f;"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Current Price:&lt;/strong&gt; $74&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color: #332f4f;"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ticker:&lt;/strong&gt; APO&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color: #332f4f;"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Market Cap:&lt;/strong&gt; $32.3B&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color: #332f4f;"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;P/E Ratio:&lt;/strong&gt; 8.54&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color: #332f4f;"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Dividend Yield:&lt;/strong&gt; 2.82%&lt;/span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Oct 2021 23:15:19 +0300</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.moby.co/blog/private-equity</link>
      <guid>https://www.moby.co/blog/private-equity</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Top 3 Military, Space &amp; Aircraft Stocks</title>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;This week was absolutely huge for the military, space, and aircraft sectors.&lt;/strong&gt; During this past week there were two major conferences. The first was the U.S. Army's annual meeting and the second was the National Business Aviation Association's (NBAA) conference in Las Vegas. Both of these two conferences are annual events that cannot be missed by investors who are actively watching the space.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color: #332f4f;"&gt;From the early conversations we had with attendees, corporations and others, the general gist is that &lt;strong&gt;2021 was a record year across aeronautics, travel, and defense.&lt;/strong&gt; Within each sub-sector, revenue growth was huge and there was hard positive spikes from 2020.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color: #332f4f;"&gt;Within travel specifically, we saw demand spiking in aircraft purchases (across retail,&amp;nbsp;corporate &amp;amp; government). And within the defense space, we saw that the US Army has and will continue to expand spending on their military presence in the Pacific Ocean.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color: #332f4f;"&gt;But while increased spending is good for the sector, only a handful of those companies will be direct beneficiaries of these huge budgets. So who are they? &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h5&gt;&lt;span style="color: #332f4f;"&gt;Let's get into it below&amp;nbsp;👇&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h5&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;&lt;span style="color: #332f4f;"&gt;Top 3 Stocks:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;&lt;span style="color: #332f4f;"&gt;1) Spirit AeroSystems (SPR)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;!-- TradingView Widget BEGIN --&gt;
&lt;div class="tradingview-widget-container"&gt;
&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;
&lt;script type="text/javascript" src="https://s3.tradingview.com/tv.js"&gt;// &lt;![CDATA[

// ]]&gt;&lt;/script&gt;
&lt;script type="text/javascript"&gt;// &lt;![CDATA[
new TradingView.MediumWidget(
  {
  "symbols": [
    [
      "State Street",
      "NYSE:SPR|12M"
    ]
  ],
  "chartOnly": false,
  "width": "100%",
  "height": 400,
  "locale": "en",
  "colorTheme": "light",
  "gridLineColor": "rgba(6, 203, 248, 0)",
  "trendLineColor": "#06cbf8",
  "fontColor": "#332f4f",
  "underLineColor": "rgba(6, 203, 248, 0.3)",
  "underLineBottomColor": "rgba(6, 203, 248, 0)",
  "isTransparent": false,
  "autosize": false,
  "showFloatingTooltip": true,
  "scalePosition": "no",
  "scaleMode": "Normal",
  "fontFamily": "Trebuchet MS, sans-serif",
  "noTimeScale": false,
  "container_id": "tradingview_4b3c2"
}
  );
// ]]&gt;&lt;/script&gt;
&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color: #332f4f;"&gt;Spirit AeroSystems is a new position for us. A stock we've always had our eye on, the conference brought on a new confidence in the name and therefore we bumped it up as one of our top plays in the sector.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color: #332f4f;"&gt;If you don't know about Spirit they are the company who helps build several important pieces of the Boeing aircraft, including the fuselage of the 737, portions of the 787 fuselage, and the cockpit section of the fuselage of nearly all of its airliners.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color: #332f4f;"&gt;While the fallout from the 737 MAX hurt their business, news from the conference is that demand is starting to pick back up across their products. Additionally business travel seems to be rebounding nicely, thus creating more demand for corporate travel. While investing in Boeing is a way to play it, Spirit is even better as they create parts for multiple airplane manufacturers!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color: #332f4f;"&gt;We're assigning them a price target of $53 which represents 25% upside from today's price!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;&lt;span style="color: #332f4f;"&gt;2) 👇&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Oct 2021 17:28:41 +0300</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.moby.co/blog/military-stocks</link>
      <guid>https://www.moby.co/blog/military-stocks</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Everything you need to know this week</title>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;We're bringing you all the news you need to know for this week. This report contains news on the most important IPO this week, the crypto&amp;nbsp;world &amp;amp; earnings news. We've highlighted the most important topics in each section!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/i9Oe4SDt1tA" title="YouTube video player" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen"&gt; &lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;&lt;span style="color: #332f4f;"&gt;Crypto News:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color: #332f4f;"&gt;Bitcoin clears the $60K mark!&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color: #332f4f;"&gt;The last time bitcoin was at these levels was in April of this year. Over the last several weeks we've seen the price rise every week but this week the catalyst was due to the bitcoin ETF. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color: #06cbf8;"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;For the first time ever, it appears as if a bitcoin ETF will go live next week!&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color: #332f4f;"&gt;The ProShares Bitcoin Strategy ETF is scheduled to debut at the New York Stock Exchange on Tuesday, and experts believe the SEC is unlikely to object to the product. If this happens, a ton of money will flood into the market for bitcoin, thereby driving the price up further. As of writing this up (October 15, 2021) we believe the price should continue going up as people buy the rumor and get excited about the future. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color: #332f4f;"&gt;As we've mentioned for years now, we have and continue to be very bullish on the future of bitcoin and think it'll clear $100k!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color: #06cbf8;"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;If you want more crypto news and access to our free trading&amp;nbsp;channel on Discord just click here -&amp;gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;span style="text-decoration: underline;"&gt;&lt;span style="color: #332f4f; text-decoration: underline;"&gt;&lt;a href="https://discord.gg/DBhnJAkvHN" style="color: #332f4f; text-decoration: underline;"&gt;Crypto Discord Channel&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr /&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;&lt;span style="color: #332f4f;"&gt;Most Important IPO This Week:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;&lt;span style="color: #332f4f;"&gt;Vita Coco Company, Inc. (COCO):&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p data-mobiledoc="{&amp;quot;version&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;0.3.2&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;atoms&amp;quot;:[],&amp;quot;cards&amp;quot;:[[&amp;quot;hr&amp;quot;,{}],[&amp;quot;hr&amp;quot;,{}],[&amp;quot;hr&amp;quot;,{}]],&amp;quot;markups&amp;quot;:[[&amp;quot;strong&amp;quot;]],&amp;quot;sections&amp;quot;:[[1,&amp;quot;p&amp;quot;,[[0,[],0,&amp;quot;This week we"&gt;&lt;span style="color: #332f4f;"&gt;Launched in 2004, Vita Coco is a leader in the global coconut water category, offering plain coconut water or coconut water flavored with pineapple, peach or mango. They also sell pressed coconut water, as well as coconut oil.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color: #332f4f;"&gt;Keurig Dr Pepper (KDP), who is Vita Coco&amp;rsquo;s largest distributor, has quietly agreed to buy $20 million of stock from Verlinvest in a private placement. Verlinvest, will then own a 38% stake in Vita Coco after the IPO. Verlinvest has some serious food companies in their portfolio and it signals a big vote of confidence having them add this to their portfolio. In addition to this positive signal the financials of the company are very strong. Here are the most important points that stuck out to us:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: #332f4f;"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Robinhood has access to their IPO:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;For a brand with a very strong retail presence, depending on the size of Robinhood's order, this could help push this stock upwards given Robinhood's average user.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: #332f4f;"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Net sales increased 10% to $310M for 2020. &lt;/strong&gt;2021 will likely come with stronger numbers and we're extremely encouraged at the size of the growth. While 10% may seem low relative to the tech world, 10% in the beverage industry is very strong.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: #332f4f;"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Gross margins increased by 3% to 35%.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;While the gross margins are a bit lower than we want to see the below graph shows us their pricing power (which should allow them to grow margins every year). The chart shows each companies beverages price per ounce. What we can see is that Vita Coco charges more per ounce than basically any other company besides energy drinks, ready to drink coffee and kombucha. This is a strong sign for us to take notice of as beverage investors.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;img src="https://kajabi-storefronts-production.kajabi-cdn.com/kajabi-storefronts-production/site/2147524877/products/oLofMqDQEmbObVVi2Myw_Screen_Shot_2021-10-14_at_4.54.59_PM.png" width="568" height="221" style="display: block; margin-left: auto; margin-right: auto;" /&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color: #332f4f;"&gt;When combining the facts above in&amp;nbsp;conjunction with the management team's experience and their outlook and we actually really like this IPO. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color: #332f4f;"&gt;However as we mentioned last week, with all IPO's, getting allocations of pre-secondary market shares is the key to success. If you're able to grab these primary shares then we'd&amp;nbsp;definitely recommend locking them up! If you're not able to, we'd wait until some of the early trading volatility shakes out before allocating a portion of your portfolio to this new IPO. In the long run though, we're buyers of the name and are looking forward to tracking their growth!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr /&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;&lt;span style="color: #332f4f;"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Most Important Companies Reporting Earnings This Week:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;&lt;span style="color: #332f4f;"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Tesla&amp;nbsp;(TSLA), October 20th:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p data-mobiledoc="{&amp;quot;version&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;0.3.2&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;atoms&amp;quot;:[],&amp;quot;cards&amp;quot;:[[&amp;quot;hr&amp;quot;,{}],[&amp;quot;hr&amp;quot;,{}],[&amp;quot;hr&amp;quot;,{}]],&amp;quot;markups&amp;quot;:[[&amp;quot;strong&amp;quot;]],&amp;quot;sections&amp;quot;:[[1,&amp;quot;p&amp;quot;,[[0,[],0,&amp;quot;This week we"&gt;&lt;!-- TradingView Widget BEGIN --&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="tradingview-widget-container"&gt;
&lt;div id="tradingview_4b3c5"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;script type="text/javascript" src="https://s3.tradingview.com/tv.js"&gt;// &lt;![CDATA[

// ]]&gt;&lt;/script&gt;
&lt;script type="text/javascript"&gt;// &lt;![CDATA[
new TradingView.MediumWidget(
  {
  "symbols": [
    [
      "State Street",
      "NASDAQ:TSLA|12M"
    ]
  ],
  "chartOnly": false,
  "width": "100%",
  "height": 400,
  "locale": "en",
  "colorTheme": "light",
  "gridLineColor": "rgba(6, 203, 248, 0)",
  "trendLineColor": "#06cbf8",
  "fontColor": "#332f4f",
  "underLineColor": "rgba(6, 203, 248, 0.3)",
  "underLineBottomColor": "rgba(6, 203, 248, 0)",
  "isTransparent": false,
  "autosize": false,
  "showFloatingTooltip": true,
  "scalePosition": "no",
  "scaleMode": "Normal",
  "fontFamily": "Trebuchet MS, sans-serif",
  "noTimeScale": false,
  "container_id": "tradingview_4b3c5"
}
  );
// ]]&gt;&lt;/script&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Tesla is a beast - there should be no doubt about it. While we did write a post recently about China trying to beat Tesla at their own game (see it: &lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration: underline;"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.moby.co/blog/china-tesla"&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;), Tesla is still in a league of their own. While Tesla does not have the backing of a government to make sure their company survives, they have the best technology and are true masters of their craft.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color: #06cbf8;"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;If you want to see our entire analysis on them just click: &lt;span style="text-decoration: underline;"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.moby.co/blog/robots-hyperloop-starlink-and-more-is-the-tesla-hype-warranted-2" style="color: #06cbf8; text-decoration: underline;"&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color: #332f4f;"&gt;But in the shorter term, we're using this earnings call to get updates on their supercharger network, Q4 expected car deliveries and YoY sales growth. But with a true hot start to earnings season so far, we expect Tesla to follow suit and report better than expected numbers. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color: #06cbf8;"&gt;While their outlook while likely drive home the stock price, we believe they beat on expectations drive the price higher.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color: #332f4f;"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Nasdaq&amp;nbsp;(NDAQ), October 20th:&lt;/span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;div class="tradingview-widget-container"&gt;
&lt;div&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;script type="text/javascript" src="https://s3.tradingview.com/tv.js"&gt;// &lt;![CDATA[

// ]]&gt;&lt;/script&gt;
&lt;script type="text/javascript"&gt;// &lt;![CDATA[
new TradingView.MediumWidget(
  {
  "symbols": [
    [
      "State Street",
      "NASDAQ:NDAQ|12M"
    ]
  ],
  "chartOnly": false,
  "width": "100%",
  "height": 400,
  "locale": "en",
  "colorTheme": "light",
  "gridLineColor": "rgba(6, 203, 248, 0)",
  "trendLineColor": "#06cbf8",
  "fontColor": "#332f4f",
  "underLineColor": "rgba(6, 203, 248, 0.3)",
  "underLineBottomColor": "rgba(6, 203, 248, 0)",
  "isTransparent": false,
  "autosize": false,
  "showFloatingTooltip": true,
  "scalePosition": "no",
  "scaleMode": "Normal",
  "fontFamily": "Trebuchet MS, sans-serif",
  "noTimeScale": false,
  "container_id": "tradingview_4b3c7"
}
  );
// ]]&gt;&lt;/script&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color: #332f4f;"&gt;&lt;span color="#332f4f" style="color: #332f4f;"&gt;Do you remember when we wrote up Nasdaq over the summer? If not see the post: &lt;span style="text-decoration: underline;"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.moby.co/blog/a-great-company-about-to-explode-in-growth"&gt;here.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color: #332f4f;"&gt;&lt;span color="#332f4f" style="color: #332f4f;"&gt;Since we wrote them up they're up now over 17% and are on the way towards hitting our price target!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color: #332f4f;"&gt;&lt;span color="#332f4f" style="color: #332f4f;"&gt;As with the rest of the financials sector, Nasdaq is benefitting from some serious tailwinds. And with earnings set to be announced later this week, we see more upside coming their way. With over $2.9B in revenue last year (15% YoY Growth), and profit growth of 20%, Nasdaq is in a position to generate more growth like we've seen over the last few years.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color: #06cbf8;"&gt;With expectations higher due to the start of earnings season, we still think Nasdaq has a good chance to beat expectations!&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color: #332f4f;"&gt;Blackstone&amp;nbsp;(BX), October 21th:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;div class="tradingview-widget-container"&gt;
&lt;div&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;script type="text/javascript" src="https://s3.tradingview.com/tv.js"&gt;// &lt;![CDATA[

// ]]&gt;&lt;/script&gt;
&lt;script type="text/javascript"&gt;// &lt;![CDATA[
new TradingView.MediumWidget(
  {
  "symbols": [
    [
      "State Street",
      "NYSE:BX|12M"
    ]
  ],
  "chartOnly": false,
  "width": "100%",
  "height": 400,
  "locale": "en",
  "colorTheme": "light",
  "gridLineColor": "rgba(6, 203, 248, 0)",
  "trendLineColor": "#06cbf8",
  "fontColor": "#332f4f",
  "underLineColor": "rgba(6, 203, 248, 0.3)",
  "underLineBottomColor": "rgba(6, 203, 248, 0)",
  "isTransparent": false,
  "autosize": false,
  "showFloatingTooltip": true,
  "scalePosition": "no",
  "scaleMode": "Normal",
  "fontFamily": "Trebuchet MS, sans-serif",
  "noTimeScale": false,
  "container_id": "tradingview_4b3c6"
}
  );
// ]]&gt;&lt;/script&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color: #332f4f;"&gt;The last company on our list is Blackstone. Last we wrote them up &lt;a href="https://www.moby.co/blog/blackstone-group-access-the-private-markets"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;(see here for original analysis)&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;it was March and the stock was trading at $76. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color: #332f4f;"&gt;Fast forward to today and the stock is at $123 - giving you a gain of 62% in only 7 months!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color: #332f4f;"&gt;We hope you were able to profit on the upside, but if not, do not fret. There is still some time left. With Blackstone due to report later this week, we see strong numbers being reported. As a huge manager of private assets and real estate, Blackstone should be profiting like crazy for the rest of 2021 and beyond.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color: #332f4f;"&gt;We therefore are continuing to hold our position. We are watching closely to this earnings call to see if there is any update on their real estate holdings going forward. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color: #06cbf8;"&gt;In any case we expect another beat and more stock appreciation going forward!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div data-mobiledoc="{&amp;quot;version&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;0.3.2&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;atoms&amp;quot;:[],&amp;quot;cards&amp;quot;:[],&amp;quot;markups&amp;quot;:[],&amp;quot;sections&amp;quot;:[[1,&amp;quot;p&amp;quot;,[[0,[],0,&amp;quot;Always a sought after recurring event, the Fed chairman" s="" press="" conference="" is="" a="" great="" way="" for="" investors="" economists="" to="" peer="" inside="" of="" the="" mind="" governmental="" entity="" that="" sets="" our="" entire="" monetary="" policy="" often="" nitpicking="" every="" word="" said="" this="" event="" an="" amazing="" see="" what="" fed="" planning="" on="" doing="" 1="" p="" 0="" as="" recent="" mr="" powell="" has="" been="" changing="" his="" tone="" around="" inflation="" historically="" he="" always="" very="" definitive="" in="" saying="" transitory="" however="" there="" have="" cracks="" message="" lately="" may="" be="" longer="" than="" expected="" markets="" reacted="" change="" narrative="" by="" selling="" off="" steeply="" at="" end="" last="" week="" july="" 16th="" they="" rebounded="" quickly="" rising="" sharply="" next="" trading="" day="" quick="" correction="" and="" jump="" back="" up="" shows="" how="" fickle="" can="" because="" we="" do="" not="" true="" thoughts="" yet="" believe="" will="" shed="" light="" into="" regarding="" should="" continue="" stating="" ride="" higher="" say="" opposite="" here="" stay="" some="" capacity="" would="" sell-off="" thereafter="" right="" now="" all="" signs="" point="" towards="" being="" foreseeable="" future="" it="" impossible="" predict="" actually="" t="" miss="" likely="" move="" either="" direction=""&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;
&lt;h2 style="text-align: center;"&gt;&lt;span style="color: #06cbf8;"&gt;Get 2-3 Free Stocks!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;h2 style="text-align: center;"&gt;&lt;img src="https://kajabi-storefronts-production.kajabi-cdn.com/kajabi-storefronts-production/site/2147524877/products/6Shg8ExXTraMJVoG5P2L_-_1_.jpg" width="298" height="167" /&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color: #332f4f;"&gt;We'd be&amp;nbsp;doing you all a disservice if we didn't share our favorite brokerage app to use: &lt;strong&gt;WeBull&lt;/strong&gt;. WeBull is by far our favorite trading platform, where we get unlimited free trades of stocks, ETFs, options and margin!&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color: #06cbf8;"&gt;And right now, if you sign up with us, you'll get up to 3 free stocks!&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span style="color: #332f4f;"&gt;Just click the link&amp;nbsp;below to claim 2-3 free stocks.&amp;nbsp; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h5 style="text-align: center;"&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration: underline;"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color: #fa4441; text-decoration: underline;"&gt;&lt;a href="https://bit.ly/2XFH4xW" style="color: #fa4441; text-decoration: underline;"&gt;Claim My Free 3 Stocks&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h5&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Oct 2021 16:26:53 +0300</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.moby.co/blog/week-ahead</link>
      <guid>https://www.moby.co/blog/week-ahead</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Moby Live: Crypto, Earnings, Sofi, Outlook &amp; More!</title>
      <description>&lt;h2&gt;&lt;span style="color: #06cbf8;"&gt;&lt;b&gt;The Following is a transcript of the most recent episode of Moby&amp;rsquo;s weekly live discussion about the stock market.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;&lt;span style="color: #06cbf8;"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Want access to the podcast as it is recorded live every single week? Join our discord: &lt;/b&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration: underline;"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://discord.gg/DBhnJAkvHN" style="color: #06cbf8; text-decoration: underline;"&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color: #332f4f;"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Peter Starr:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400;"&gt; And now coming to you live from our coast to coast trading desk. This is Moby.co live, a weekly live podcast discussing stocks, the economy, and the mechanics that make your money grow.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400; color: #332f4f;"&gt;I'm your host, Peter Starr. I'm joined as always by moby.co co-founder and our lead analyst, Justin Kramer. Justin, what's good? How's life over in your false autumn. You got going on?&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color: #332f4f;"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Justin Kramer:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400;"&gt; Good So far! Can't complain every day in the markets. It&amp;rsquo;s been a crazy week in the markets&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color: #332f4f;"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Peter Starr:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400;"&gt;&amp;nbsp; Yeah, that seems to be the major theme. Like usually Q4 is when you see the most heat on the economy and it's just, we have a very hot economy already. So watching all of this volatility, there's a lot of noise coming at our market reports this week. There's not a lot of signal to latch onto.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400; color: #332f4f;"&gt;There's so many like disparate things at play. Crypto is on a tear right now, but at the same time oil and energy prices are high. So supply chains are still messy and we've got demand and volatility for days. But I guess the best place to start is the latest earnings calls in banks and other services rapidly driving the S&amp;amp;P up right now at the very end of the day right before close here on Thursday.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400; color: #332f4f;"&gt;What's the deal? What's driving these really huge earnings calls that are just shooting the market up?&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color: #332f4f;"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Justin Kramer:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400;"&gt; Yeah, It's a great question. And there's a few things going on here. One of them is just sales. If you look at the supply chain, something we've been talking about for a bit now, it's so backed up.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400; color: #332f4f;"&gt;And so demand is also backed up and tense. So, when some supply issues get fixed, the demand starts to pick up and that creates this cyclical effect that &amp;nbsp; spirals into each other, where you get this increase in demand that happens quarter over quarter as more supply gets there.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400; color: #332f4f;"&gt;And then ultimately you see this growth and numbers, quarter over quarter. So when the most recent earnings report &amp;nbsp; came out to lead this week, it got, I think, surpassed some people's expectations and that's why the market really started running off. And then some of the inflationary stuff seems to be a little bit &amp;nbsp; ignored for now.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400; color: #332f4f;"&gt;Shockingly, we saw the markets sit down, um, not too bad yesterday when they announced it, but I want to think we want to start more of a reaction, but I guess there, the earnings are really. You know, making sure that the other stuff is ignored more or less. But the talk with interest rates starting to creep back up since springtime.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400; color: #332f4f;"&gt;So now a lot of the banks too are starting to &amp;nbsp; pop back up as interest rates talks as fed talks to raise interest rates overall, profitability, the interest on their outstanding. And that's why we saw JP Morgan, Bank of America. A lot of those kinds of finance stocks pop up, um, today. And then also over the last year.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color: #332f4f;"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Peter Starr:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400;"&gt; Exactly. And it's one of those things where, you know, we are still seeing a lot of supply chain woes, but it's one of those things where that's only driving stock prices down. As people can't quite match demand, the moment they match that demand, it just completely pops off in terms of profitability. So the fact that demand is just high right now for some companies who can figure it out, who can vertically integrate, it's going to be a great thing, but the main thing driving this rally is services obviously, and banking too, based on the back of interest rates. And so that &amp;nbsp; gets me to one of the major reports you did this week.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400; color: #332f4f;"&gt;Justin, we've talked about the market as a whole really quickly, so let's dive into some specifics. I wanted to hear about some of your thoughts on a specific piece of analysis you did this week. Specifically,&amp;nbsp; I'm talking about SoFi.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400; color: #332f4f;"&gt;Since they IPO&amp;rsquo;d this year, SoFi has been a really controversial stock.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400; color: #332f4f;"&gt;And I wanted to get some more in-depth thoughts from you in terms of what their future is like. Obviously this year, it's all about financial services. If you even mentioned the word FinTech, like within 50 feet of a VC, they will just hurl a =can money at you. So there's a lot of that interest.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400; color: #332f4f;"&gt;There's a lot of demand there too, but why, SoFi specifically? You've had a really bullish view on what&amp;nbsp; SoFi is doing to grow.&amp;nbsp; What&amp;rsquo;s you view on what &amp;nbsp; SoFi is doing to make sure that they establish really strong position?&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color: #332f4f;"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Justin Kramer:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400;"&gt;&amp;nbsp; Well, first real quick: you were talking about just like, how investors are selling to FinTech. And I was just saying before I jumped into, so by brief recap on where we stand, because obviously as you mentioned, investors were showing up into FinTech, right.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color: #332f4f;"&gt;We got a lot of investor attention and we&amp;nbsp;just&amp;nbsp;raised our seed round very recently. So if you guys missed the news, we announced it on Instagram, but we just closed out our initial seed round of funding, which we're super excited about. And we're super excited about it because we're going to be scaling up, hiring like crazy.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400; color: #332f4f;"&gt;We're going to be bringing on a ton of new writers and engineers and designers, um, new analysts. I mean, you name it like we're going to be hiring. And so we're really excited to &amp;nbsp; expand our product, bring new teachers and continue building on honestly what we're doing now. I&amp;rsquo;m really excited to have all you guys &amp;nbsp; here as early adopters.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400; color: #332f4f;"&gt;So, back to SoFi: It's a boring answer, but it was always &amp;nbsp; an easy stock to hate. They were as part of the SPAC trend, they were part of the off trend and a lot of what he was putting out at the time. In retrospect, it was just a lot of noise.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400; color: #332f4f;"&gt;However, looking back so far, it&amp;rsquo;s one of these few SPAC companies that&amp;rsquo;s doing well. They&amp;rsquo;re diversifying and integrating.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400; color: #332f4f;"&gt;They have the ability to trade crypto. They offer a lot for what they're doing so different is their go to market is primarily scoped around credit.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400; color: #332f4f;"&gt;And if you're not familiar with credit or you don't have credit debt-- credit is an extremely dry, boring topic that people just &amp;nbsp; ignore till they need it. But what SoFi&amp;nbsp; is doing, which is really different and unique, is that they're leading with credit for the younger generation.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color: #332f4f;"&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400;"&gt;So for people who have student loans who have debt for whatever reason, or are &amp;nbsp; sucking them in giving them either lower rates or an easier platform to do. Yeah, our &amp;nbsp; overall wound needs. And then once they're there, especially for a lot of the ones that are extending these 10, 20, 30 year loans, by the time that person pays them back, which&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span style="font-weight: 400;"&gt;&amp;nbsp;is obviously a long period of time, they then suck them in with their other products.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400; color: #332f4f;"&gt;So that's where the investing kicks in. That's where the crypto kicks in. That's where they're applying for a bank charter right now that they want to hopefully do your banking. You're trying to be like a one-stop shop for all your financial needs were point-based Obviously they're super deep into crypto.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400; color: #332f4f;"&gt;You have Robinhood, obviously super deep into brokerage and you have all these other players within the consumer FinTech space. We're &amp;nbsp; specializing in some sort of niche. SoFi has &amp;nbsp; taken the opposite approach and more or less is trying to, could you, everything that you need as an individual.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400; color: #332f4f;"&gt;So if you need a credit union, bank, or all the things I mentioned before, they may do it for you. And so the overall go to market is a lot harder to acquire you. But once they do acquire them, the metrics we've been looking at now that they're public is that they hold onto them better than pretty much anyone else in the industry.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400; color: #332f4f;"&gt;And, you know, lifetime value, which is basically how much they track that of every single user is far superior to everyone else. And so they're really just in the early stages of starting to ramp up scale of their platform of who they were. Um, and, and money they got from going public is certainly like help is going to gear them towards&amp;nbsp; like that next generation of the company.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400; color: #332f4f;"&gt;So long story short, when we started looking under the hood to see what the most recent numbers were and &amp;nbsp; their overall differentiation versus everyone else, we got super bullish on the future of the company and the growth over the next year. Especially when a bank charter hopefully gets approved.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400; color: #332f4f;"&gt;I think relative to Robinhood and a lot of other financial services stocks it isn't being priced in and they didn't gain the hype, everyone else has. So that's where we see a lot of the upside. We put it into our models for a projection. Can we really honestly think that the market is just missing a big opportunity here.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400; color: #332f4f;"&gt;A lot of stocks are getting hurt right now. So it may take a bit for this one to fully be realized. I think this time next year, when people are starting to look at the earnings and the numbers, they aren't just projections and they're real. That's when a lot of this is going to start to come to.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color: #332f4f;"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Peter Starr:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400;"&gt; And to really drive this home for you audience, I want to just point out, I want to do a very quick analogy here to really like lock this in one thing that's really important to keep in mind is that right now, this moment is a moment of very cheap capital for services, specifically financial services.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400; color: #332f4f;"&gt;And the analogy I want to use here is -- back in like the early 2010s, 2013 to 2016, we saw really cheap capital for e-commerce and Amazon took advantage of that and vertically integrated and became the one-stop shop for all life on earth, for e-commerce. And that's how they dominated. You're seeing a very similar dynamic play out here with SoFi. Everyone else is trying to specialize. Whereas&amp;nbsp; SoFi is literally trying to own your entire financial journey from the moment you exit university to the point where you need to start a family to everything else you need credit wise and like growing your wealth.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400; color: #332f4f;"&gt;So I'm also really bullish on SoFi looking at those factors, because they can just keep borrowing to like, first of all, services are the&amp;nbsp; game in town right now. And at the same time, financial services just have such great margins that they're going to be able to get really good capital for a really long time.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400; color: #332f4f;"&gt;So I'm also very excited for it. We'll be, we'll be checking back in Q2 2022 to see how Justin's really aggressive position played out there for now though. Let's get into our next topic. So we D we try to talk about specific stocks when we try to look at the economy as a whole. It's really great to be in services right now, really excited about it.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400; color: #332f4f;"&gt;But what I'm concerned about now is our general inflation worries. We talked a lot about supply chain last week. We've talked a lot about lots of inflationary pressure at ports and stuff, but I think one thing too, now we're seeing a lot of weird things like oil. The energy crisis in Europe is starting to hit the U S.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400; color: #332f4f;"&gt;All not an all-time high, but like a relative high today as well. What's going on in terms of oil and food, , Justin, what are you, what are you thinking about in terms of inflation? Like everyone thinks it's transitory, but what's, what are your thoughts in terms of just like all the heat in our economy right now?&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color: #332f4f;"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Justin Kramer:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400;"&gt; It's a good point. And it's really interesting right now because the reports come out in the U S most recently that that inflation is running quite more rampant than like the fed cares to even still, frankly, Um, and then you have in Europe to your point, a lot of stuff going on gas in the U S there's food.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400; color: #332f4f;"&gt;I mean, social security also, I think it was just increased by the most. It has been in the last decade. So there's a lot of indications that inflation is not transitory and that it's been here for some time and will continue to be here for some time. Right. The Fed's in an interesting position right now, because in order to combat inflation, they typically use a handful of tactics, but given &amp;nbsp; where they sit with interest rates, where they see the outlook for COVID and given where they stand &amp;nbsp; in a global economy, that tools at their disposal are interesting in terms of what they're able to actually do.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400; color: #332f4f;"&gt;Going forward to fight inflation. I think that the market has shown its resilience over the last few years through COVID through a lot of scares. And so that's why on days like today we see like more rebounds when corporate earnings go up. The long-winded way of saying these are real problems in the economy, but until there is a real &amp;nbsp; question mark on certain sectors that are weeding the S&amp;amp;P so like really right now, it's healthcare finance, financials and tax.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400; color: #332f4f;"&gt;I don't really see that dragging down the market over the long-term, even with any hiccups in, you know, bad and markings of economic indicators. So you saw the most, very recently, you saw the most amount of people quit their jobs voluntarily over the last quarter event ever before. Well, and there's a whole supply shortage on the actual non-skilled side of the waiver for, so people are finding better opportunities.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400; color: #332f4f;"&gt;People are making money. Companies are making money. As they're starting to, I continue to &amp;nbsp; scale up their operations. Inflation is becoming an issue. It will be an issue. Um, I don't think that again, I don't think I would drag down. There, there may be an interesting, and I think we're far from it, but I think there may be an interesting inflection point where inflation runs so rampant that people are starting to be discouraged from spending overall, which then we'll have a really robust.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400; color: #332f4f;"&gt;The actual corporate earnings. But again, until that point happens I don't think we're at yet. I, I don't think that most American investors, especially on the institutional side are going to be taking their money out of these asset classes. Anytime soon you look across the economy to, there's not really a better place right now to find upside as interest rates.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400; color: #332f4f;"&gt;So fixed income instruments are a 30 year loan. I'm not really going to be pouring their money into it. It's&amp;nbsp; the best of the worst right now. So it's a long-winded way of saying it's a problem, but I don't really see a dragging down the stock market for a long period.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color: #332f4f;"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Peter Starr:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400;"&gt; And it is complicated because what it is really is heat, right?&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400; color: #332f4f;"&gt;It's when you look at the inflationary pressures,&amp;nbsp; Like when you learn about this and like macroeconomics, like 1 0 1 and 2 0 1, you think just about in terms of monetary supply, but the inflationary pressures we're seeing are all the results of supply chain issues. The cost of getting anything into the United States right now is astronomical.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400; color: #332f4f;"&gt;The cost of getting energy to or out of Europe is ridiculous. And therefore, you're just what you're seeing is those &amp;nbsp; like fundamental foundational costs rippling across making inflation happen rather than like, there's just too much money in the economy, which I guess you could still say, like there's more money in the U S economy than there ever has been before, but there's also more productivity, so it can go either way.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400; color: #332f4f;"&gt;So when they say inflation is transitory, they're talking about that in terms of the inflationary pressures, themselves being transitory, the port of LA and long beach is open 24 7. And so there is a small chance that this could be a transitory situation as well, given that the inflationary pressures are &amp;nbsp; those real world ones where costs are rising in places where they are solvable.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400; color: #332f4f;"&gt;Either way, when we get into another report you did, as we&amp;nbsp; get to the back half of this here, Justin, one thing you see too, you mentioned, first of all, 4.3 million people voluntarily quit their jobs in the last quarter, which is the most ever, which is staggering and that's of 6.3 separations, which means two thirds of the people who don't have jobs anymore quit.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400; color: #332f4f;"&gt;And that also means that ties into the unemployment report that came out today, which wasn't as bad as it should be with that many people out of work.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400; color: #332f4f;"&gt;So the question is where did these people go? And at the same time we think about food inflation. We're seeing those skilled labor Leave that labor pool entirely and therefore lots of smaller restaurants and lots of small businesses dry up in America. And so you're seeing the&amp;nbsp; classic story of the last 20 years where small players&amp;nbsp; get dried out where big players come in, when you're looking in that food space.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400; color: #332f4f;"&gt;Justin, in a recent report you outlined three companies that you think are &amp;nbsp; like the Kings there, when you're those big, one of those bigger companies that have a lot of that supply chain, how can you take advantage of a situation like this and how do you see a lot of growth happening in the food space?&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color: #332f4f;"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Justin Kramer:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400;"&gt; Yeah, no, it's an interesting point. And on the unemployment rate side, what a lot of people actually don't realize is that the unemployment rate is a function of people looking for work. So all those people that quit their job actually aren't counted in the unemployment rate they got, they're not actively looking for work.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400; color: #332f4f;"&gt;So the number is actually going to be a bit understated. But having said that, the true reason why all these people have quit their jobs, it feels easy out there to figure it out. So I'm assuming there's greener pastures. But until there's actually definitive data, it's hard to point to any single factor, but yeah, so &amp;nbsp; transitioning over onto the food part.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400; color: #332f4f;"&gt;It's really interesting because to your point there there's so much inflation right now and COVID like fundamentally changed the food business. 90,000 restaurants closed independently. And it represents 4% of the United States GDP. And so it's obviously a massive impact on the economy and a lot of local businesses, obviously we're the ones who had to bear the brunt of this.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400; color: #332f4f;"&gt;While a lot of corporate chains were able to &amp;nbsp; keep pushing on. They invest in technology. You don't have to worry about supply chain issues as much since they're dealing directly with distributors and manufacturers. So. It's unfortunate, but the reality is that a lot of money started moving more towards these large corporate chains, people who have scale and reach, and then the local shops that are obviously important for culture and important for the local economy are getting pushed to the side.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400; color: #332f4f;"&gt;So it's, it's, it's a sad story, but it's a continuation of things we've seen for a while now. It got really amplified with COVID. Um, so that's why that article, that post, that we pushed out, we talked about the companies that are able to. You know, circumvent a lot of the issues that the small businesses in America are facing.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400; color: #332f4f;"&gt;So when you look at your brands, you look at McDonald's and you look at Domino's, you know, they're not the sexiest companies out there that are go double a year over a year, but there are companies that are, they don't have to worry about the supply chain as much. And if they do, they have pricing power, they're invested deeply in technology.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400; color: #332f4f;"&gt;So for delivery for integrations with third party, They don't have to nearly worry as much, or if they do, they have the money to &amp;nbsp; continue on any, , continued path, any issues. Um, and so when you look at their sales numbers, they're, they're, they're as strong as they've ever been. And Domino's specifically is an interesting one because even pre pandemic therapy business, that has one of the, it has been one of the best IPO's can throw in 2000 and they've returned an insane amount of capital over the years to shareholders they're growing like crazy.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color: #332f4f;"&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400;"&gt;It's a name that a lot of people sleep on because it's a, it's a pizza company, but these companies and companies like them, other, other chains, not all of the chains, because Starbucks is having some issues. Um, they're going to continue. Doing really&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400;"&gt;]&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400;"&gt; well. And then you see it with like the wealth captain America, between the rich and the poor, the, divide between corporate food versus local food is going to continue widening, which again is unfortunate, but it's just the reality of the world we live in.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400; color: #332f4f;"&gt;So as investors, these are &amp;nbsp; like the stocks and it's actually companies. We need to be careful.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color: #332f4f;"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Peter Starr:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400;"&gt; And that makes a lot of sense. And that does tie into the whole conversation we've been having.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400; color: #332f4f;"&gt;So audience, when you, when you see this&amp;nbsp; inflationary pressure, when you're thinking about how to invest in sort of this very hot environment, the main thing you need to keep in mind is, is during these periods where costs are going up, it's going to be the larger players who can, who can vertically integrate and take over their supply chain who are going to survive.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400; color: #332f4f;"&gt;Whereas you can see that a lot, a lot of food services companies specifically in a lot of small businesses only survived because of how low wages were allowed to be for the last 20 years. And so once you have wage pressure rising, all of those businesses &amp;nbsp; get wiped out. So when you're thinking about trying to build your portfolio right now, it's less about looking for moon behavior. It's less looking for those huge. 50 to 75% upside in a year. And just making sure that you are beating the market as much as possible as your investments become your main inflation hedge.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400; color: #332f4f;"&gt;So you think in that growth mindset, as opposed to overly cautious, this is the time to be medium aggressive&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color: #332f4f;"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Justin Kramer:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400;"&gt; People are just getting so ahead of themselves. They saw Bitcoin go up 10 X, 20 X in the last few years. They&amp;rsquo;ve seen so many investments radically increase in size. I think the days of having these crazy outside your terms for honestly, relatively low risk are what about behind us for the medium term.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400; color: #332f4f;"&gt;So to your point, you should be looking for companies that are a little bit lower risk that still offer upside, but aren't going to 10 or 20x.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400; color: #332f4f;"&gt;It's A boring answer, but honestly, the people who are out there searching for the 10, 20 X are taking such ridiculous risk that yeah, maybe they'll get it. I know they'll find a coin.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400; color: #332f4f;"&gt;They'll find a stock. They'll find a company that can do that for them. But for every one person who's able to do that. There's going to be 99% of people who fail. And it's an unfortunate answer. Because obviously everyone wants to be making as much money as possible all the time. The environment we're in right now, that's the maturity of even the crypto industry, which is a hilarious thing to say within itself.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400; color: #332f4f;"&gt;I think that, like, if you think this is going to continue again, where you can, put money into an NFT or put money into a stock and expect it to two, three X in one year, and there's multiple, I'm doing that. I think those days are behind us for a bit. And especially on the NFT side, we even saw the market cool off there.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400; color: #332f4f;"&gt;So I know I'm getting a little bit of a tangent here. On the energy side. A lot of the money now is going towards the creators of the end of the day, the people who are mentoring them and the sellers are making money, but not nearly as much as they were even six months ago, people who are actually making it, selling it, doing the creation.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400; color: #332f4f;"&gt;That's where the money is. It&amp;rsquo;s going to be had on the exchanges where the selling happens. It's a cycle right now where people are greedy and they're, and they're looking for assets that can rapidly appreciate. I just think a lot of people are going to get burned pretty, pretty hard.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color: #332f4f;"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Peter Starr:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400;"&gt; Honestly.Yeah. It's one of those things where the have all of the markets that heated up the fastest, it was the NFT market. Like it was even faster than the altcoin boom&amp;nbsp; we sawin 2017, 2018. Like it's been absolutely wild watching these on chain assets come out of nowhere. So I'm really excited to see what happens to this very crowded, very hot space in web three, but that does give us a very nifty transition Justin into right now.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400; color: #332f4f;"&gt;We only have, we have one real question from the audience The only question I got so far from our audience, obviously our audience is very excited about crypto. I mean,Bitcoin being up what? $10,000 in like the last week and a half, a lot of altcoins sort of picking up as well. So a real quick call here, Justin:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400; color: #332f4f;"&gt;Ethereum, or Solana what's your pick?&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color: #332f4f;"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Justin Kramer:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400;"&gt;Like what timeframe?&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color: #332f4f;"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Peter Starr:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400;"&gt; I would say medium term, because we're living in that medium term moment. I'm sure the question was for the short term, like which one's gonna have the biggest pump, which you can't ever predict in the short term, but medium term metrics.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400; color: #332f4f;"&gt;Like when you're looking at the big player or the small player in. How do you feel in terms of who has that better medium term?&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color: #332f4f;"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Justin Kramer: &lt;/b&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400;"&gt;Yeah. I mean, it's all a&amp;nbsp; function of risk. It's like, do you want to be taking on a ton of risk yet? If the answer is yes and so on and definitely is going to offer a lot more upside than any theory in is if you're looking for something that's a little bit more stable and at the end is the end of the day.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400; color: #332f4f;"&gt;Solana again, this is so ridiculous that I'm even saying this on as a little bit past the point where it's going to go up 10 X while the rest of the market goes up is relatively flat. Those coins out there. If you're seeking those crazy returns, those are the ones that are a little bit more off the beaten path.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400; color: #332f4f;"&gt;Whereas Solana is not at&amp;nbsp; Etherems level yet, obviously, but starting to get to the point where it's going to say. So large that it starts to track the broader crypto market. So if the crypto goes up 10, maybe it goes up 12 or, or maybe it goes up five, but you're taking on significantly more risk and chasing, not as much upside.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400; color: #332f4f;"&gt;So it's a long-winded way of saying think you should have exposure to both. If you're trying to minimize your risk, I'd rather go with Ethereum, but Solana over the next five years has attached, still has a ton of time we're outside. So I like it as a longer term tech, but in a shorter medium, I think, um, if your income is, if you look at a price chart and so on to create, starting to consolidate around the one 50 level, there, there obviously could be breakouts.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400; color: #332f4f;"&gt;Ethereum, based on the technical analysis we've done so far that you continue &amp;nbsp; going that way until there's any, some sort of a catalyst. If it, all of a sudden it goes up 20, 30%. So it shows the rest of crypto. It's not going to be having any sort of breakout.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color: #332f4f;"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Peter Starr:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400;"&gt; No, I love that. And that really&amp;nbsp; cements what we've been talking about for this whole conversation.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400; color: #332f4f;"&gt;We went, we had a winding road with the whole economy we had here. We had a lot of really good discussions about, , inflation, about service, the services economy, about everything that &amp;nbsp; goes through, um, just the heat that we're seeing in the economy right now. And the ultimate answer to every single question that we had today was think medium term.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400; color: #332f4f;"&gt;Long-term, it's really hard to tell. Like how big risk is short-term is going to be mayhem, but medium two to five-year term, that's where you're going to see how you're going to chart the best possible path through this period of, I don't think it's going to be years of inflation, so to speak. I think we're going to power through the supply chain issues and then supply will catch up to demand and that'll be just a super fun period in the market.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400; color: #332f4f;"&gt;Maybe Q3 2022 Q1 2023. But the main thing to keep in mind is you have to think medium now, and that's going to be how you make sure that your wealth keeps up with costs as they continue to rise. So just in a really, I'm&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color: #332f4f;"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Justin Kramer:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400;"&gt; going to say the people. Yeah, because the people out there who saying, oh, Solana is going to be at a thousand dollars in five, 10 years from now, or are going to do this.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400; color: #332f4f;"&gt;Most people who say stuff like that are full of shit. There's no fundamentals. Like there it's a team that has a ton of funding and a lot of these projects have a ton of fun. They're so early in their business, if you look at any venture capitalist or any like investor who is, who truly has like a, , an understanding of what's going on a lot of is a crapshoot.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400; color: #332f4f;"&gt;So like there's no fundamental way to say it's going to be at here an X date. A lot of it is you fundamentally believe in the project, in the investors, in the people working at the company. Um, and so do you believe in them? And it's like, there's no way to quantify, but that's how you have to think about some of these longer term projects.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400; color: #332f4f;"&gt;To your point in the medium term, in a shorter term, there are certain things we can look for and we can use technical analysis and we can look at the broader &amp;nbsp; pricing trends of the industry. But I mean, for, for everyone who's listening now, if. You hear Gary V and you hear some of these people get on and just talk about how this coin has gone to the moon in the next 10 years.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400; color: #332f4f;"&gt;A lot of it is just pure speculation, or they have underlying motives for wanting to pump a lot of these coins. Like that's something, especially in the crypto industry. Honestly, got to watch out&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color: #332f4f;"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Peter Starr:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400;"&gt; for, especially in the defy space, especially when you're thinking about the ecosystem being built by Ethereum and Solana.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400; color: #332f4f;"&gt;Just thinking about it in terms of an asset class is &amp;nbsp; the wrong way of thinking about it right now. The main thing, the main energy you can get out of web three that is Solano and Ethereum and those kinds of adjacent defy blockchains. Yeah. Being part of that infrastructure. Like there's a lot of people who are slowly but surely learning how to code, whatever that weird language is.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400; color: #332f4f;"&gt;You have to code to make a theory of contracts and Solana contracts, but there's a lot of work out there too. So you should be looking into a lot of these communities and seeing what dowels are coming out, people looking for folks to help build those projects because that's real. I mean, well, it's real Solana, whatever.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400; color: #332f4f;"&gt;But it's one of those things where if you're a part of a building class on web three, it's probably a lot more upside than just buying and holding. If it's one of those things where if you're thinking about side hustles, if you're thinking about, , adding to your productivity, Do you have a lot of upside from taking your skills and donating to that?&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400; color: #332f4f;"&gt;Not necessarily donating them, but bringing them to a web three platform like anybody building on top of Ethereum and Solana. And that's maybe how you should be thinking when you're in this very inflation, heavy state, it's going to be actually. Building that's going to help your wealth go up. Not necessarily just the &amp;nbsp; financialization we've seen so far, but either way, Justin, it's been a really awesome conversation.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400; color: #332f4f;"&gt;I appreciate you sticking with, do you have any final thoughts for us? Anything else on the back end here, man? Anything you want us to keep in mind as we roll through to the end of the weekend, the rest of October.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color: #332f4f;"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Justin Kramer:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400;"&gt; Yeah, 100% right now is like investors. And it's been like this for a while and it will continue to be like this, the volatility, the choppiness, is tough to stomach, but that's why, again, we say it every day and we sound probably boring and like broke records at this point.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400; color: #332f4f;"&gt;But if you're in a five, 10 year time horizon, then this, day-to-day bullshit doesn't matter.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400; color: #332f4f;"&gt;As you need to be paying attention to the economy and you need to be paying attention, but once you initiate or you buy one of the things we recommend, because you fundamentally believe in what we're saying, and we believe in the stocks and the investments as well, like don't be looking at your portfolio every single day.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400; color: #332f4f;"&gt;Don't be staring at the stock gains, go up and down. You're just going to drive yourself crazy. All it takes. It's like, if you fundamentally believe in it today, unless anything has changed over the next year or the next two years, then there's no reason you need to be selling this stock. Anytime soon, the crypto side of things, we are doing active trade.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400; color: #332f4f;"&gt;So that's something that we are flipping daily, weekly, monthly. So that's something you need to be aware of. But when there are stocks that we're saying we're holding for multi-year periods, just deal with the volatility. It sucks. You can't be measuring your wealth to the. You were worth a hundred K six months ago, and now you're worth 90K.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400; color: #332f4f;"&gt;You can't be like I'm down 10K&amp;nbsp; and you just investing doesn't work like that. You can't be measuring yourself from your high point. There's going to be dips. There's going to be. Anyone who's been invested in crypto for over five years. Fundamentally knows that. So I'll leave everyone with there's volatility in the market today.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400; color: #332f4f;"&gt;When you fundamentally believe that the markets will continue to trend upwards over the next few years and the stocks we put out while they will experience upside and downside for the next several months and quarters. And these are things we fundamentally believe in, and yes, we're not going to be right down a hundred percent of what we do.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400; color: #332f4f;"&gt;Yeah, I think our track record has spoken pretty well for what we have.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color: #332f4f;"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Peter Starr:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400;"&gt; And that's a hell of a bow to put on that. And I think one thing you keep, you, you keep talking about boring as if it's like this negative thing, but in an economy like this boring is beautiful folks. Like you need to go boring. Our attention economy is so hot right now, too.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400; color: #332f4f;"&gt;Like everyone, the only way you can get ahead is by. Just being as loud as possible and saying the sky is falling or saying that Bitcoin's going to go to 200 K by December any of this wild stuff, you have to keep in mind that a lot of the noise comes from the market pressures within our actual knowledge economy to do all of the noise isn't quite as good as the actual signal, which is medium.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400; color: #332f4f;"&gt;15 to 20% gains year over year and just, you know, holding the.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400; color: #332f4f;"&gt;That's how you're going to win in this period. Either way, I really appreciate your time audience. Thank you so much for being here with us.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: 400; color: #332f4f;"&gt;Thank you so much for your time. And as always, I like to leave you with peace, love and incremental gains. Everyone be well, thank you so much.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Oct 2021 21:42:35 +0300</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.moby.co/blog/moby-live</link>
      <guid>https://www.moby.co/blog/moby-live</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why China May Beat Tesla at Its Own EV Game</title>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color: #332f4f;"&gt;Experts are calling for China to overtake the US as the world's largest economy by the year 2030. Their rise in power over the last 40 years from poverty to somewhat of a comfortable middle class life has been astonishing. Even though Beijing and the central government still have full control over everything that goes on within their borders, the meteoric rise in wealth is unprecedented.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color: #06cbf8;"&gt;And now China is establishing the future of their economy in a new way via Electric Cars.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color: #332f4f;"&gt;While this may come as a surprise to some, China is actually a green energy powerhouse. They produce more solar panels, wind turbines and lithium ion batteries than any other country in the world. By 2030, it is estimated that they'll control most of the clean energy jobs and wealth and that is why we're predicting that they'll be at the center of EV's going forward. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color: #332f4f;"&gt;While China is extremely polluted, their incentive to get into green energy is purely opportunity based and the money is right before their eyes. Right now they are the largest market by EV's by sales in the world. 5% of sales there are EV's and 40% should be there by 2030. While they were late to the game on combustion based engines, they are surely not letting this opportunity pass them by. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color: #332f4f;"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The reason they've been able to capitalize on this opportunity is due to the 863 initiative that kicked off in 2001.&lt;/strong&gt; They invested&amp;nbsp;$130M in fuel cell, EV and hybrid development. This investment has since guided their clean energy development over the last 15 years. They want to be the world leader in EV's in order to further supplant the US and become the world's largest economic player.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color: #332f4f;"&gt;But since historically the car market has not done well international within China's borders, many of the American consumers and investors do not know who the biggest companies of tomorrow will be. Pair that with some serious governmental pressures, and not only do you need to project the right companies who will do well but you need to have a good sense of the geo-political climate and which companies have good relationships with the government. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color: #332f4f;"&gt;Therefore we created the list below to find the perfect cross section between the two!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color: #06cbf8;"&gt;So with that long intro, here are 3 companies who have a chance to see some serious upside in the EV sector!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;&lt;span style="color: #332f4f;"&gt;1) Geely (GELYF):&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color: #332f4f;"&gt;Geely is an OTC stock that is huge in China! They bought Volvo from Ford and have a stake in Daimler. While they aren't selling as many cars as Tesla, they are rapidly testing new technologies. They also want to build 20,000 charging points and battery swaps stations across china.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color: #332f4f;"&gt;When looking at their current reach, we see they have cars that they sell for only $5,000 and are only 15 feet long. The benefits of this are obvious. With such small cars they are not only affordable but can be used anywhere within an urban setting.&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;85% of miles driven in china is done locally as&amp;nbsp;people don't travel far. &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color: #332f4f;"&gt;With less distance, range becomes less important - thereby satisfying the needs of Chinese consumers becomes quite easy.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color: #332f4f;"&gt;And the government is helping them like crazy! They are incentivizing users to buy them by:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: #332f4f;"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;They created lanes in many Chinese cities where EV's can go and combustion engines cannot.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;Because traffic is such a problem in China, having this special ability makes a huge difference for many Chinese consumers.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: #332f4f;"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;EV buyers get subsidies for buying these cars.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;Further pushing them to make the change.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: #332f4f;"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Getting parking permits for combustion engines is very hard.&lt;/strong&gt; Whereas getting it for EV's is easy and with such small cars you can split a space for half the cost!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: #332f4f;"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The government helped create 1.68M charging points relative to the 72,000 in the US.&lt;/strong&gt; Therefore adoption becomes much easier!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color: #332f4f;"&gt;This all adds up to an unreal experience! Add in the fact that Geely has an amazing relationship with China (something that is paramount for being successful) and we see them achieving huge feats over the next decade. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color: #332f4f;"&gt;This is a long term play and will likely take some time to play out but is an amazing way to play the Chinese EV market!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color: #332f4f;"&gt;2)&amp;nbsp;⬇️&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Oct 2021 22:04:10 +0300</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.moby.co/blog/china-tesla</link>
      <guid>https://www.moby.co/blog/china-tesla</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Our Top 3 Restaurant Stocks</title>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color: #332f4f;"&gt;It is no secret that restaurants were one of the hardest hit sectors in the economy during the pandemic. But the stats on how hard they were hit are frankly mind-blowing. Here's a list of some of the most shocking numbers:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: #332f4f;"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;90,000 restaurants&amp;nbsp;closed permanently during the pandemic in the US alone.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;4% of US GDP is attributed to the food and restaurant industry and this number represents a massive amount of that industry going away almost overnight (it is estimated that $290B in revenue was lost from 2020-2021). &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: #332f4f;"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The industry employs 11,000,000 people and 16,000,000 total including other parts of the food supply change.&lt;/strong&gt; Not only will it hurt the industry but it also put a ton of people out of work (unemployment&amp;nbsp;rate is twice the national average) - thereby ruining lives and further hurting small businesses.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: #332f4f;"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;In order to combat the issues many government rolled out grants to try and help restaurants&amp;nbsp;by providing them with funds. &lt;/strong&gt;As good as their intentions were, distributing&amp;nbsp;the funds was another whole dilemma. The funds quickly became exhausted in many cities and many restaurants&amp;nbsp;suffered because they were not able to claim the proceeds. With fall and winter around the corner, many restaurant owners are scared it'll mess things up again especially with the variants floating around.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color: #332f4f;"&gt;As terrible as all this is, it fundamentally changed the face of the food industry forever. And guess what?&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;Big chains and corporate arms were able to profit while local businesses got crushed.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align: left;"&gt;&lt;span style="color: #332f4f;"&gt;This is large part happened because chains were able to adapt quickly&amp;nbsp;because they invested in technology whereas local restaurants, with smaller amounts of cash reserves, were not able to overcome the challenges as fast. Pair that with supply chain issues and spikes in commodity prices, and local business suffered hard. And the scary thing is these challenges are far from over. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 style="text-align: left;"&gt;&lt;span style="color: #06cbf8;"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Therefore as investors, we need to be ready to adapt as quickly as possible to the changing dynamics across the globe. &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align: left;"&gt;&lt;span style="color: #332f4f;"&gt;So &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="color: #332f4f;"&gt;we created the list below to show which companies have and will continue to benefit as much as possible from the dynamics currently in play!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color: #332f4f;"&gt; This is a can't miss list for investors eyeing opportunities in the food &amp;amp; beverage industry!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;&lt;span style="color: #332f4f;"&gt;Our Top 3 Restaurants Stocks:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color: #332f4f;"&gt;1) Yum! Brands, Inc. (YUM)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;!-- TradingView Widget BEGIN --&gt;
&lt;div class="tradingview-widget-container"&gt;
&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;
&lt;script type="text/javascript" src="https://s3.tradingview.com/tv.js"&gt;// &lt;![CDATA[

// ]]&gt;&lt;/script&gt;
&lt;script type="text/javascript"&gt;// &lt;![CDATA[
new TradingView.MediumWidget(
  {
  "symbols": [
    [
      "State Street",
      "NYSE:YUM|12M"
    ]
  ],
  "chartOnly": false,
  "width": "100%",
  "height": 400,
  "locale": "en",
  "colorTheme": "light",
  "gridLineColor": "rgba(6, 203, 248, 0)",
  "trendLineColor": "#06cbf8",
  "fontColor": "#332f4f",
  "underLineColor": "rgba(6, 203, 248, 0.3)",
  "underLineBottomColor": "rgba(6, 203, 248, 0)",
  "isTransparent": false,
  "autosize": false,
  "showFloatingTooltip": true,
  "scalePosition": "no",
  "scaleMode": "Normal",
  "fontFamily": "Trebuchet MS, sans-serif",
  "noTimeScale": false,
  "container_id": "tradingview_4b3c2"
}
  );
// ]]&gt;&lt;/script&gt;
&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color: #332f4f;"&gt;If you're not familiar with YUM they are behind the brands such as KFC, Pizza Hut, Taco Bell, The Habit Burger Grill, and WingStreet worldwide. They did over $5.6B in revenue last year and are an absolute behemoth in the food and beverage industry! &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color: #332f4f;"&gt;Similar to&amp;nbsp;the stock below, YUM is one of our top food stocks as they can manipulate prices, control the supply chain and hedge inflation better than almost anyone else can. Similar to the other stocks YUM is a safe pick that pays out a dividend with more growth potential than the stock below. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color: #332f4f;"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;But what makes YUM so different is their ability to hedge any trouble in China.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color: #332f4f;"&gt;Via their China operations - YUM China, YUM is able to avoid a lot of pain other companies like Starbucks are feeling. YUM has a solid relationship with the growing superpower and should continue to be able to assert their global dominance for years to come. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color: #332f4f;"&gt;We therefore have given YUM's price target 18% upside to where it currently trades.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color: #332f4f;"&gt;2)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Oct 2021 22:07:37 +0300</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.moby.co/blog/restaurant-stocks</link>
      <guid>https://www.moby.co/blog/restaurant-stocks</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
